<quotelist>
<quote epno='1.03' title='Homers Odyssey'>
Marge: There, there, Homer, You've caused plenty of industrial accidents and you've always bounced back.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.03' title='Homers Odyssey'>
Sherri: Hey, Bart. Our dad says your dad is incompetent.
Bart: What does "incompetent" mean?
Terri: It means he spends more time yakking and scarfing down donuts than doing his job.
Bart: Oh, okay. I thought you were putting him down.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.05' title='Bart the General'>
Homer: The code of the schoolyard, Marge! The rules that teach a boy how to be a man! Let's see; don't tattle, always make fun of those different from you, never say anything unless you're sure everyone feels exactly the same way you do.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.06' title='Moaning Lisa'>
Bleeding Gums Murphy: The blues isn't about making yourself feeling better, it's about making other people feel worse.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.06' title='Moaning Lisa'>
Bleeding Gums Murphy: [to Lisa] You know, you play pretty well for someone with no real problems.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.07' title='The Call of the Simpsons'>
Lisa: Remember, Dad. The handle of the Big Dipper points to the North Star.
Homer: That's nice, Lisa, but we're not in astronomy class. We're in the woods. 
</quote>
<quote epno='1.08' title='THe Telltale Head'>
Homer: [on Heaven] I can understand how they wouldn't let in those wild jungle apes, but what about those really smart ones who live among us who roller-skate and smoke cigars?
</quote>
<quote epno='1.08' title='THe Telltale Head'>
Bart: Well, I was wondering... how important is it to be popular?
Homer: I'm glad you asked, son. Being popular is the most important thing in the world.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.11' title='The Crepes of Wrath'>
Marge: Deportation?! You mean kick Bart out of the country?!
Homer: Hear him out, Marge. 
</quote>
<quote epno='1.12' title='Krusty Gets Busted'>
"Krusty": Hand over all your money in a paper bag.
Apu: Yes, yes, I know the procedure for armed robbery. I do work in a convenience store, you know.
Apu: [to Homer] You can emerge now from my chips. The opportunity to prove yourself a hero is long gone.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.13' title='Some Enchanted Evening'>
Moe: [to Homer]See? You're a pig. Barney's a pig. Larry's a pig. We're all pigs. Except for one difference: once in a while, we can crawl out of the slop, hose ourselves off, and act like human beings.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.13' title='Some Enchanted Evening'>
Ms. Botz: You're a smart, young man, Bart! I hope you're smart enough to keep your mouth shut!
Lisa: He isn't.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Otto: Hey, Bart Dude. Woah, you look freaked!
Bart: Otto, man, I have a test today that I'm not ready for! Could you please crash the bus or something?
Otto: Sorry, Bart Dude. Can't do it on purpose. But hey, maybe you'll get lucky!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Bart: Say, who's up for a little cram session? I'll go first. What was the name of the Pilgrims' boat?
Sherri: The Spirit of St. Louis.
Bart: And where'd they land?
Terri: Sunny Acapulco.
Bart: And why'd they leave England?
Sherri: Giant rats.
Bart: [writing down the information in a notebook] Cool, history's coming alive!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Martin: As a natural enemy, I don't know why I should care. But the information you received regarding America's colonial period is erroneous.
Bart: Meaning....
Martin: A blindfolded chimp with a pencil in his teeth has a better chance of passing this test than you do!
Bart: Thanks for the pep talk...
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Bart: Look at my eyes! See the sincerity? See the conviction? See the fear? As God is my witness, I can pass the fourth grade!
Homer: And if you don't, at least you'll be bigger than the other kids. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.02' title='Simpson and Delilah'>
Homer: D'oh! [stops strangling Bart] Dirty trick. Okay, I'm not going to kill you, but I'm going to tell you three things that are gonna haunt you for the rest of your days. You've ruined your father, you've crippled your family, and baldness is hereditary!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.03' title='Treehouse of Horror'>
Lisa: [reading] "Quit throwing your garbage into our dimension!"
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Mr. Burns: Ironic, isn't it Smithers. This anonymous clan of slack-jawed troglodytes has cost me the election, and yet if I were to have them killed, I would be the one to go to jail. That's democracy for you!
Smithers: You are noble and poetic in defeat, sir. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Barney Gumble: Oh no! An election! It's one of those deals where they close the bars isn't it?
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Homer: Bart, would you like to say grace?
Bart: Dear God, we paid for all this stuff ourselves, so thanks for nothing. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Homer: For the first time in my life, people weren't laughing at me, they were laughing towards me!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Marge: A Simpson on a T-shirt, I thought I'd never see the day.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Homer: I wonder why stories of degradation and humiliation make you more popular?
Moe: I don't know. They just do. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Homer: Marge, where's the Duff?!
Marge: Oh, uh, we're all out, Homer.
Homer: D'oh!
Marge: Would you like some fruit juice?
Homer: Don't toy with me, woman! 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Marge: Homer. I couldn't help overhearing you warp Bart's mind.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Lisa: Bart, having never received any words of encouragement myself I'm not sure how they're suppose to sound, but here it goes. I believe in you.
Bart: Thanks man. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Homer: C'mon Bart. Remember what Vince Lombarde said- "If you lose, you're out of the family."!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.07' title='Bart vs Thanksgiving'>
Grampa: Homer was never stubborn. he always folded instantly over anything. It was as if he had no will of his own. Isn't that true Homer?
Homer: Yes Dad. 
</quote>

<quote epno='2.07' title='Bart vs Thanksgiving'>
Grampa: Let's go. If I'm not back at the home by 9 they declare me legally dead and collect my insurance!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.08' title='Bart the Daredevil'>
Bart: Otto, I'm going to leap over Springfield Gorge on my skateboard.
Otto: You know, Bart, as the only adult here, I feel I should say something.
Bart: What?
Otto: COOOOOOOOL!!!!!
</quote>

<quote epno='2.08' title='Bart the Daredevil'>
Lance Murdock: It's always nice to see young people taking an interest in danger. Now, son, a lot of people are going to be telling you you're crazy - and maybe they're right! But I want to tell you three things: bones heal, chicks dig scars, and the United States of America has the best doctor-to-daredevil ratio in the world!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.10' title='Bart Gets Hit by a Car'>
Lionel Hutz: Hutz is the name, Mr. Simpson. Lionel Hutz, attorney-at-law. Here's my card. It turns into a sponge when you put it in water.
Homer: Ooh, classy.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.11' title='One Fish, Two Fish, Blowfish, Blue Fish'>
Dr. Hibbert: Now, a little death anxiety is normal. You can expect to go through five stages. The first is denial.
Homer: No way, because I'm not dying!
Dr. Hibbert: Second is anger.
Homer: [yelling] Why you little!
Dr. Hibbert: After that comes fear.
Homer: [worried] What's after fear? What's after fear?!
Dr. Hibbert: Bargaining.
Homer: Doc, you gotta get me outta this. I'll make it worth your while.
Dr. Hibbert: Finally acceptance.
Homer: Well, we all gotta go sometime.
Dr. Hibbert: Mr. Simpson, your progress astounds me.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Barney: Hey Homer! You're late for English!
Homer: English, who needs that? I'm never going to England. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Homer: [tries to ask Marge to the prom] Look, I'm not asking you to like me. I'm not asking you to put yourself in a position where I can touch your goodies. I'm just asking you to be fair.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Flashback Homer: Marge I have a problem. When you stop this car, I'm gonna hug you. And kiss you. And I'll never be able to let you go.
Present Homer: And I never have. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.13' title='Homer vs. Lisa and the 8th Commandment'>
Homer: [referring to Lisa] There's something wrong with that kid. She's so moral. Why can't she be more like...Well, not like Bart. But there has to be a happy medium. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.14' title='Principal Charming'>
Marge: It's Patty who chose a life of celibacy. Selma simply had celibacy thrust upon her.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.14' title='Principal Charming'>
Marge: You will find Selma a man!
Homer: All right.
Marge: And not just any man.
Homer: Okay!
Marge: He should be honest, and, and caring. And well-off. And handsome.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Bart: No way, she's faking! If Lisa stays home, I stay home.
Lisa: If Bart stays home, I'm going to school.
Bart: Fine, then... Wait a minute... If Lisa goes to school, then I go to school, but then Lisa stays home, so I stay home, so Lisa goes to school...
Marge: Lisa, don't confuse your brother like that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Mrs. Winthrop: Let me tell you the two most importand words you will ever hear in your life - "choke chain!"
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Martin: How can we tell if we're doing this maneuver effectively?
Mrs. Winthrop: The dog's eyes will bulge and his tongue will protrude and change color ever so slightly.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.17' title='Old Money'>
Marge: You know, we'll be old someday.
Homer: Gasp! My God, you're right, Marge! You kids wouldn't put me in a home like I did to my dad, would you?
Bart: Well...
Homer: Aaah! 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.17' title='Old Money'>
Grandpa:[asking a lady out on a date] Well, I was wondering if you and I you know, might go to the same place at the same time and... Jeez! You'd think this would get easier with time!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.18' title='Brush with Greatness'>
Burns: [offscreen] SMITHERS! I WANT MY TEA!
Marge: [to Smithers] Doesn't it bother you that he orders you around like that?
Smithers: [chuckles] Actually, I value every second we're together. From the moment I squeeze his orange juice in the morning, till I tuck him in at night. He's not just my boss, he's my best friend too. [Burns enters; Smithers gives him the tea]
Burns: [sipping] Bah! Too hot! [throws it on Smithers]
Smithers: Right, sir. It's... scalding me as we speak. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.19' title='Lisas Substitute'>
Mr. Bergstrom: Lisa, your homework is always so neat. How can I put this? Does your father help you with it?
Lisa: No. Homework's not my father's specialty.
Mr. Bergstrom: Well there's no shame in it, I mean, my dad--
Lisa: Not mine.
Mr. Bergstrom: You didn't let me finish--
Lisa: Unless the next word was "burped", you didn't have to. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.19' title='Lisas Substitute'>
Homer: Hey! Just because I don't care doesn't mean I don't understand!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Dr. Hibbert: [Homer is passed out on the floor as everyone leaves Marge's party.] If you want him to live through the night, I suggest you roll him onto his stomach.
Marge: Thank you, Doctor.
Dr. Hibbert: Remember, I said "if."
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Homer: About last night. You might have noticed Daddy acting a little strange and you probably don't understand why.
Bart: I understand why. You were wasted.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Homer: I admit it. I didn't know when to say "when." I'm sorry it happened and I just hope you didn't lose a lot of respect for me.
Bart: Dad, I have as much respect for you as I ever did or ever will.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.22' title='Blood Feud'>
Marge: The moral of this story is a good deed is its own reward.
Bart: Hey, we got a reward. The head is cool!
Marge: Well then... I guess the moral is no good deed goes unrewarded.
Homer: Wait a minute! If I hadn't written that nasty letter, we wouldn't have gotten anything!
Marge: Well... then I guess the moral is the squeaky wheel gets the grease.
Lisa: Perhaps there is no moral to this story.
Homer: Exactly! It's just a bunch of stuff that happened.
Marge: But it certainly was a memorable few days.
Homer: Amen to that!
</quote>

<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Homer: Marge, I can't wear a pink shirt to work. Everyone wears white shirts. I'm not popular enough to be different.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Michael Jackson: I can't believe you've never heard of me, I'm a very popular entertainer.
Homer: of course I've heard of you! I mean you'd have to be living under a rock not to know...what'd you say you name was?
Michael Jackson: Michael Jackson.
Homer: Doesn't ring a bell.
Michael Jackson: Well have you heard of MTV?
Homer: No
Michael Jackson: Motown?
Homer: No
Michael Jackson: Beat it?
Homer: You beat it!
Michael Jackson: Thriller?
Homer: What was that last one again?
Michael Jackson: Thriller.
Homer: No. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Homer: Wow! How do you do that thing with your feet?
Michael Jackson: The moonwalk?
Homer: NO! That thing with your feet!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Doctor: Mr. Simpson, after talking to your wife we believe you're no threat to yourself or others.
Homer: That's the most flattering thing anyone has ever said to me. Can I have it in writing? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: Who would've guessed reading and writing would pay off?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: Wow a shoehorn! Just like in the movies! Shoe goes on. Shoe goes off. Shoe goes on. Shoe goes off.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: I had a feeling it was too good to be true. Every time you get a million dollars, something queers the deal.
Lisa: I don't think real checks have exclamation points. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: [reading] Then I heard the sound that all Arctic explorers dread... the pitiless bark of the sea lion! [gasp] He'll be killed!
Marge: Homer, he obviously got out alive if he wrote the article.
Homer: Don't be so... [flips ahead] Oh, you're right. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Faith Crowley: And here are your V.I.P. badges. These will get into place regular tourists never get to see!
Homer: Oh, miss! What does the "I" stand for?
Faith Crowley: Um..."Important."
Homer: Oh, okay. What about the "V"?
Faith Crowley: "Very."
Homer: Miss, just one more qu...
Faith Crowley: "Person."
Homer: Uh-huh. (pause) What does the "I" stand for again? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.03' title='When Flander Failed'>
Homer: [On the phone] Hello, Jerry? Homer Simpson. Remember last month when I paid back that loan? Well now I need YOU to do a favor for ME.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.04' title='Bart the Murderer'>
Chief Wiggum: Fat Tony is a cancer on this fair city. And I am the... um... What cures cancer?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Kent Brockman: Uh, Mr. Burns, people are calling this a meltdown.
Mr. Burns: [over the hotline] Oh, meltdown. It's one of these annoying buzzwords. We prefer to call it an unrequested fission surplus. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Mr. Burns: Well Smithers, I guess there's nothing left to do but kiss my sorry ass good-bye.
Smithers: May I, sir?
Mr. Burns: Ewww... 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Apu: Oh Otto! Otto! Do you know there is a small child inside your bus?
Otto: Oh, good thing you warned me. I was on my way to Mexico. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Homer: Well ya know boys. A nuclear reactor's a lot like a woman. You just have to read the manual and press the right buttons.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.06' title='Like Father, Like Clown'>
Krusty: (voice-over) My father was the most respected person in the Lower East Side of Springfield. People would come for miles around to ask his advice.
Young Jewish Man: Reb Krustofsky, should I finish college?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Yes. No one is poor, except he who lacks knowledge.
Jewish Woman: Rabbi, should I have another child?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Yes. Another child would be a blessing on your house.
Jewish Man: Rabbi, should I buy a Chrysler?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Could you rephrase that as an ethical question?
Jewish Man: Um... is it right to buy a Chrysler?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Oh, yes! For great is the car with power steering and dyna-flow suspension. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.07' title='Treehouse of Horror II'>
Burns: [Burns transplants Homer's brain into a robot] Smithers, hand me that ice-cream scoop.
Smithers: Ice-cream scoop?!
Burns: Dammit, Smithers! This isn't rocket science, it's brain surgery!
Mister Burns: [Burns removes Homer's brain then puts it atop his own head] Look at me, I'm Davy Crockett!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Lisa: Dad, I broke my last saxophone reed, and I need you to get me a new one.
Homer: Uh, isn't this the kind of thing your mother's better at?
Lisa: I called her. She's not home. I also tried Mr. Flanders, Aunt Patty, Aunt Selma, Dr. Hibbert, Reverend Lovejoy, and that nice man who caught the snake in our basement.
Homer: Wow, and after them, out of all the people in the world, you chose me.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Marge: Hmmm, we're in serious trouble here. We're just going to have to cut back on luxuries.
Homer: Well, you know, we're always buying Maggie vaccinations for diseases she doesn't even have.
Marge: Actually, I was thinking we could cut back on your beer.
Homer: Nah, we're not gonna be doing that.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Marge: Alright, you got us into this, you get us out.
Homer: Fine! I will! There's plenty of money out there for a guy who's willing to work for it. (Pauses) You have any jewelry you don't need anymore? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Horse Trainer: Although there is no change in my patrician facade, I can assure you my heart is breaking. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Bart: Hey, how come Lisa gets a pony!
Homer: Because she stopped loving me.
Bart: I don't love you either, so get me a moped.
Homer: I know you love me so you get squat. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.09' title='Saturdays of Thunder'>
Homer: You know, Marge, that Bart is a little miracle, his winning smile, his button nose, his fat little stomach, his face alight with wholesome mischief. He reminds me of me before the weight of the world crushed my spirit.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.09' title='Saturdays of Thunder'>
Homer's Brain: Don't you get it? You've got to use reverse psychology.
Homer: That sounds too complicated.
Homer's Brain: OK, don't use reverse psychology.
Homer: All right, I will! 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Moe: It's like there's a party in my mouth, and everyone's invited.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Homer: Moe, I haven't seen the place this crowded since the government cracked down on you for accepting food stamps.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Miss Krabaple: Bart! Are those liquor bottles?
Bart: I brought enough for everbody.
Miss Krabaple: Take those to the teacher's lounge. You can have what's left at the end of the day 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Stockbroker: Homer, it's your stockbroker. Your stock in the powerplant just went up for the first time in 10 years.
Homer: I own stock!
Stockbroker: Yes, all the employees got some in exchange for waving certain constitutional rights. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Carl: Yeah, you know, those Germans aren't so bad.
Lenny: Sure they made mistakes in the past, but hey, that's why pencils have erasers! 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
German Managers: Attention workers, we have completed our evaluation of the plant. We regret to announce the following lay-offs, which I will read in alphabetical order... Simpson, Homer. That is all.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Mr. Burns: What good is money if you can't inspire fear in your fellow man?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Homer: Do you really think you're pregnant?
Marge: Well, I have the same nausea and craving for pancake mix I had with the other kids.
Homer: Yeah, and I have the same tightness in my chest and profuse sweating I always did. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Clerk: Basic ceremony's twenty bucks. Here's your license. (She hands them a punch card.) Be sure to get this punched every time. The tenth wedding is on the house!
Homer: Hey! This marriage is gonna last forever!
Clerk: (chuckling) No matter how many times I hear that, it still makes me laugh!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Homer: Marge, look at this! A baby monitor! (into the monitor) "Baby to Marge. Baby to Marge. Waa! Waa! Over."
Marge: Homer, I don't know how we can afford all these things on your salary. [Homer looks out the window and sees the Power Plant.]
Homer: Hey, why don't I apply at the Nuclear Power Plant. I hear they pay pretty well!
Marge: I don't know. I heard radiation can make you sterile.
Homer: Pfft. Now you tell me!
</quote>

<quote epno='3.13' title='Radio Bart'>
Kent: So, as it turns out, we've all been victims of a cruel hoax, masterminded by a 10-year old hooligan. The time has come for finger-pointing, and most of them are squarely aimed at the boy's parents.
Homer: It's not our fault! We didn't want the boy, he was an accident!
Marge: HOMER!
Homer: Sorry. Uh... could you edit that last part out?
Kent: Mr. Simpson, we're live, coast-to-coast.
Homer: D'oh!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.15' title='Homer Alone'>
Selma: Lisa, you'll sleep in my bed. Bart, you'll be sleeping with your Aunt Patty.
Bart: ...In your bed?
Patty: Uh-huh. And just a warning: I'm told I snore. [Patty and Selma chuckle. Bart and Lisa quickly grab each others hand]
Patty: Oh! "Divorce Court" is on in five minutes! [They get up and leave.]
Bart: I'm scared, Lisa.
Lisa: You think you know fear? Well, I've seen them naked! [Bart screams] 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.19' title='Dog of Death'>
Chief Wiggum: No, you got the wrong number. This is nine-one... two.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.19' title='Dog of Death'>
Smithers: People like dogs, Mr. Burns.
Burns: Nonsense! Dogs are idiots. Think about it, Smithers: if I came into your house and started sniffing at your crotch and slobbering all over your face, what would you say?
Smithers: [pause] If you did it, Sir? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Redneck #1: Hey you! Let's fight!
Redneck #2: Them's fightin' words!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Studio Manager: You know, this studio has a lot of history. Buddy Holly stood on that same spot in 1955 and said, "There is no way in hell I am recording in this dump!"
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Marge: [after seeing Lurleen] I thought you said she was overweight.
Homer: Marge, it takes two to lie. One to lie, and one to listen. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.21' title='Black Widower'>
Marge: Now, now, he's an ex-convict! He's paid his debt to society!
Patty: Then how come you're not using the good silverware?
Marge: I'm just not. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.22' title='The Otto Show'>
Marge: Why don't you go and live with your parents?
Otto: Oh, the admiral and I don't get along. Please let me stay here. I've got nowhere else to go!
Homer: Forget it. That line didn't work for my dad, and it's not gonna work for you.
Marge: Homer, I know we didn't ask for this, but doesn't the Bible say, "Whatever you do unto the least of these my brothers, that you do unto me?"
Homer: Yes, but doesn't the Bible also say, "Thou shalt not take moochers into thy...hut?" 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.22' title='The Otto Show'>
Bart: You can do it, Otto. You're the coolest adult I've ever met.
Otto: Wow! I've never been called an adult before. I've been tried as one, but... I'll do it!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.23' title='Barts Friend Falls in Love'>
Milhouse: Let me try. Will I get beat up today? [shakes the ball] "All Signs Point To Yes."
Nelson: That ball knows everything. [bashes Milhouse on the head.]
</quote>
<quote epno='3.24' title='Brother Cand You Spare Two Dimes?'>
Lisa: [At Homer's hastily-concocted award ceremony] This show is the biggest farce I ever saw!
Bart: What about the Emmys?
Lisa: I stand corrected.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.01' title='Kamp Krusty'>
Homer: Son. If you really want something in this life, you have to work for it. Quiet! They're gonna announce the lottery numbers. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.01' title='Kamp Krusty'>
Lisa: You're serving us gruel?
Dolph: Not quite. [pulls out a large drum of gruel with Krusty's face on the front] This is Krusty-Brand Imitation Gruel. Nine out of ten orphans can't tell the difference. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.03' title='Homer the Heretic'>
Marge: Homer, don't make me chose between my man and my God, because you just can't win.
Homer: There you are. Always taking someone else's side; Flanders, the water department, God... 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.03' title='Homer the Heretic'>
Homer: God?
God: [points finger at Homer] THOU HAST FORSAKEN MY CHURCH!
Homer: But Lord, I am not a bad man. I work hard and provide for the welfare of my family. So why should I be forced to spend half my Sunday listening about how I am going to Hell anyway?
God: You have a good point there. Sometimes, even I would rather be watching football. Does Saint Louis still have a team?
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Shopkeeper: Take this object, but beware it carries a terrible curse!
Homer: [worried] Ooooh, that's bad.
Shopkeeper: But it comes with a free Frogurt!
Homer: [relieved] That's good.
Shopkeeper: The Frogurt is also cursed.
Homer: [worried] That's bad.
Shopkeeper: But you get your choice of topping!
Homer: [relieved] That's good.
Shopkeeper: The toppings contains Potassium Benzoate.
Homer: [stares]
Shopkeeper: That's bad.
Homer: Can I go now?
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Mr. Burns: [about bringing Marge along on their voyage] What do you think, Smithers?
Smithers: I think women and seamen don't mix.
Mr. Burns: We know what you think. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Lisa: Thank God we didn't turn into a bunch of mindless zombies.
Bart: Shhh! TV! [The family stare blankly at the television. A thud is heard, followed by a laugh track.]
Homer: Man... fall down. Funny.
Family: Mmmmmm... 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.07' title='Marge Gets a Job'>
Smithers: This resume is very impressive. Let me be the first to say Abibu gazini.
Marge: What?
Smithers: "Welcome aboard." I guess my Swahili's not as good as yours. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.08' title='New Kid on the Block'>
Homer: [to Bart and Lisa] SHUT UP, YOU LITTLE MONSTERS! [to the phone] I was wondering if you'd like to babysit my little angels. [On the other end of the line...]
Woman: I'm sorry, this isn't Abby. This is her sister. I look after her now. [Abby rocks in her chair and mumbles quietly to herself.]
Abby: No, Bart... put it down... put it down, Bart... put it down...
</quote>
<quote epno='4.08' title='New Kid on the Block'>
Homer: You see, son, a woman is a lot like... err... a refrigerator! They're about six feet tall, 300 pounds... they... make ice... uhhh... oh! Actually, a woman is more like a beer. They smell good, they look good, you'd step over your own mother just to get one! [drains his beer] But you can't stop at one, you wanna drink another woman! [runs to the fridge]
</quote>
<quote epno='4.11' title='Homers Triple Bypass'>
Bart: Nothing you say can upset us. We're the MTV generation.
Lisa: We feel neither highs or lows.
Homer: Really? What's it like?
Lisa: Meh. [shrugs]. 
</quote>

<quote epno='4.11' title='Homers Triple Bypass'>
Homer: Don't worry Marge. America's health care system is second only to Japan... Canada, Sweden, Great Britain... well, all of Europe. But you can thank your lucky stars we don't live in Paraguay!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.12' title='Marge vs. the Monorail'>
Marge: How fast are they going?
Homer: Eeeeeyaaaaaaai! [super fast as monorail whizzes by platform]
Cobb: [looking at watch] Well, judging by your husband's cowardly scream, a hundred eighty miles an hour. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.13' title='Selmas Choice'>
Bart and Homer: (singing) On top of spaghetti all covered with cheese, I lost my poor meatball...
Marge: If you don't mind, we're on our way to a funeral!
Homer: Ding dong the witch is dead...
Bart: Which Old Witch?
Homer: The Wicked Witch! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.15' title='I Love Lisa'>
Ralph: Dad, how do you get a girl to like you?
Chief Wiggum: Son, (cracks a nut with the butt of his revolver) whether you want to win a girl or crack a nut, the key is persistence; (cracks a nut) keep at it, and never lose your cool. Chief Wiggum tries to crack a third nut, but the shell doesn't break.]
Chief Wiggum: (losing patience) Ah, come on, you stupid...! [Chief Wiggum loads his gun up and shoots the nut.]
Chief Wiggum: (angrily) Let that be a lesson to the rest of you... nuts!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.15' title='I Love Lisa'>
Homer: Is there a problem, officer?
Chief Wiggum: Yep. Got a tail-light out.
Homer: Where?!
Chief Wiggum: [Smashing a tail-light] Right there.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.16' title='Duffless'>
Otto: My name is Ot-to. I love to get blot-to!
Hans Moleman: My name is Hans. Drinking has ruined my life. I'm 31 years old!
Homer: My name is Homer and I'm just here because the Court made me come.
Lovejoy: Homer, with our help you'll never touch a beer again. [Homer screams and jumps through the window]
</quote>
<quote epno='4.17' title='Last Exit to Springfield'>
Factory Worker: You can't treat the working man this way! One day, we'll form a union and get the fair and equitable treatment we deserve! Then we'll go too far, and get corrupt and shiftless, and the Japanese will eat us alive!
Burns's Grandfather: The Japanese? Those sandal-wearing goldfish-tenders? Bosh! Flimshaw!
Mr. Burns: [to Smithers, in the present] If only we'd listened to that boy, instead of walling him up in the abandoned coke oven. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.18' title='So Its Come to This: A Simpsons Clip Show'>
Lou: That sounded like an explosion at the old Simpson place.
Chief Wiggum: Forget it. That's two blocks away.
Lou: Looks like there's beer coming out of the chimney. (Wiggum gets out of the car)
Chief Wiggum: I am proceeding on foot. Call in a Code 8.
Lou: [into radio] We need pretzels. Repeat, pretzels.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Bart: Hey Grampa, we need to know your first name.
Grampa Simpson: [gasps in horror] YOU'RE MAKING MY TOMBSTONE! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Lisa: (to Grampa) So, we wrote the cartoon, put your name on it and sent it in.
Bart: Didn't you wonder why you were getting checks for doing absolutely nothing?
Grampa: I figured, cause the Democrats were in power again. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Bart: Hey Grampa, we need to know your first name.
Grampa Simpson: [gasps in horror] YOU'RE MAKING MY TOMBSTONE! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.21' title='Marge in Chains'>
Ned: Oh, the network slogan is true! Watch Fox and be damned for all eternity!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.21' title='Marge in Chains'>
Hutz: Your Honor, my client claims that she simply forgot she was carrying this bottle of... delicious bourbon... brownest of the brown liquors... so tempting... [puts the bottle to his ear] What's that? You want me to drink you? But I'm in the middle of a trial! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Marge: Lisa, you got a letter.
Lisa: It's from my pen pal, Anya! [As Lisa reads, the letter writer's voice can be heard in voice over.]
Anya: "Dear Lisa - as I write this, I am very sad. Our president has been overthrown and...
Gruff male voice: ...replaced by the benevolent General Krull. All hail Krull and his glorious new regime! Sincerely, Little Girl." 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Chief Wigggum: I'd like to help you ma'am, but, heh heh, I'm afraid there's no law against mailing threatening letters.
Marge: [indignantly] I'm pretty sure there is!
Wiggum: Hah! The day I take cop lessons from Ma Kettle...
Lou: Hey, she's right, Chief.[Lou shows Chief Wiggum a book called "Springfield Law"]
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Wiggum: Well, shut my mouth. It's also illegal to put squirrels down your pants for the purposes of gambling. [Cut to Eddie with squirrels in his pants while the other cops watch and laugh, rolling dice]
Wiggum: Boys, knock it off!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.03' title='Homer Goes to College'>
Smithers: [The plant melting down, Mr. Burns gets into escape pod and shuts Smithers out.] For the love of God, sir, there are two seats!
Burns: I like to put my feet up.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.06' title='Marge on the Lam'>
Rescue Worker: Homer, there's no easy way to put this, but we're going to have to saw your arms off.
Homer: They'll grow back, right?
Rescue Worker: Oh... yeah.
Homer: Whew. 
</quote>

<quote epno='5.07' title='Barts Inner Child'>
Troy McClure: Hi! I'm Troy McClure! You might remember me from such self-help videos as 'Smoke Yourself Thin' and 'Get Confident, Stupid!'
</quote>
<quote epno='5.08' title='Boy-Scoutz N the Hood'>
Homer: Marge, don't discourage the boy. Weaseling out of things is important to learn. It's what separates us from the animals! Except the weasel.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.09' title='THe Last Temtation of Homer'>
Charlie: [explaining about the gas leak] Well, sir, I won't bore you with the details of our miraculous escape, but we desperately need a real emergency exit!
Burns: Why, that's a fabulous idea. Anything else you'd like? How about real lead in the radiation shields? Urinal cakes, maybe? (hands Smithers a notebook) Smithers, throw this at him! [Smithers throws the book at Charlie, and Burns presses a button. A tube covers Charlie and sucks him upwards]
</quote>
<quote epno='5.10' title='$pringfield (Or, How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling'>
Kent Brockman: Scott, things aren't as happy as they used to be down here at the Unemployment Office, joblessness is no longer just for philosophy majors... now at the risk of sounding unpopular, this reporter places the blame for all of this squarely on you (pointing at the camera) the viewers!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.10' title='$pringfield (Or, How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling'>
Lisa: Dad! You shouldn't wear glasses that weren't prescribed for you!
Homer: (looking at Bart) Lisa just because you're ten feet tall doesn't mean you can tell me what to do. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.11' title='Homer the Vigilante'>
Kent Brockman: Hordes of panicky people seem to be evacuating the town for some unknown reason. Professor, without knowing precisely what the danger is, would you say it's time for our viewers to crack each other's heads open and feast on the goo inside?
Professor: Mmm, yes I would, Kent. 
</quote>

<quote epno='5.12' title='Bart Gets Famous'>
Bart: [after Marge has convinced  him to peform one more time] You're right, Mom. I shouldn't let this bother me. I'm in television now. It's my job to be repetitive. My job. My job. Repetitiveness is my job. (To Marge) I'm gonna go out there and give the best performance of my life!
Marge: The best performance of your life?
Bart: The best performance of my life!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.12' title='Bart Gets Famous'>
Lisa: And now you can go back to just being you, instead of a one-dimensional character with a silly catch-phrase.
Homer: (breaking a lamp) D'oh!
Bart: Ay, caramba!
Marge: (groans)
Maggie: (sucks her pacifier)
Flanders: Hi-dilly-ho!
Barney: (belches)
Nelson: Ha, ha!
Burns: Excellent!
Lisa: [Long pause. Everyone looks expectantly at Lisa.] If anyone wants me, I'll be in my room.
Homer: What kind of catch phrase is that!? 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.13' title='Homer and Apu'>
Homer: Your old meat made me sick!
Apu: Oh I am so sorry. Please accept five pounds of frozen shrimp as an apology.
Homer: This shrimp isn't frozen! And it smells funny!
Apu: Okay, ten pounds.
Homer: Woo-hoo! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.13' title='Homer and Apu'>
Homer: Life is just one crushing defeat after another until you just wish that Flanders was dead.        
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Malibu Stacy Doll: Don't ask me. I'm just a girl! Tee-hee!
Bart: Right on! Say it, sister!
Lisa: This isn't funny, Bart! Millions of girls will grow up thinking that this is the right way to act - that they can never be more than vacuous ninnies whose only goal in life is to look pretty, land a rich husband and spend all day on the phone with their equally vacuous friends and talk about how damned terrific it is to look pretty and have a rich husband!
Bart:...Just what I was gonna say! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Mr. Burns: [Smithers turns his computer on. A bitmapped Mr. Burns (shown naked from the shoulders up) appears] [in stilted speech] Hello, Smithers. You're quite good at tur-ning me-on.
Smithers: [to Lisa] Um... you probably should ignore that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Stacy: I see exactly what you mean; this is a problem. But what do you expect me to do?
Lisa: Change what she says. It's your company.
Stacy: Not since I was forced out in 1974. They said my way of thinking just wasn't cost effective.
Lisa: [gasps] That's awful.
Stacy: Well, that - and I was funneling profits to the Viet Cong.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.15' title='Deep Space Homer'>
Stillwater: People, we're in danger of losing our funding. America isn't interested in space exploration anymore.
Babcock: Maybe we should finally tell them the big secret, that all the chimps we sent into space came back super intelligent. (A chair swivels around, revealing a chimp in a suit, wearing glasses, and smoking a pipe.)
Chimp: (arrogant; English accent) No, I don't think we'll be telling them that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.15' title='Deep Space Homer'>
Reporter: Uh, question for the barbecue chef: Don't you think there is an inherent danger in sending underqualified civilians into space?
Homer: I'll field this one. The only danger is if they send us to that terrible Planet of the Apes. (Homer thinks for a moment and realises something.)
Homer: Wait a minute, Statue of Liberty - that was our planet! You maniacs! You blew it up! Damn you! Damn you all to hell! 
</quote>


<quote epno='5.16' title='Homer Loves Flanders'>
Mr. Burns: [Mr. Burns talking to football players before the game] Men, there's a little crippled boy sitting in a hospital who wants you to win this game. I know because.. I crippled him myself to inspire you. [cuts to Milhouse lying in a hospital bed with a broken leg and his parents at his sid]
Milhouse: I hope they win or Mr. Burns said he's coming back. [Kirk and Luann look at each other worried] 
</quote>
</quotelist>
