<quotelist>
<quote epno='1.03' title='Homers Odyssey'>
Marge: There, there, Homer, You've caused plenty of industrial accidents and you've always bounced back.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.03' title='Homers Odyssey'>
Sherri: Hey, Bart. Our dad says your dad is incompetent.
Bart: What does "incompetent" mean?
Terri: It means he spends more time yakking and scarfing down donuts than doing his job.
Bart: Oh, okay. I thought you were putting him down.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.05' title='Bart the General'>
Homer: The code of the schoolyard, Marge! The rules that teach a boy how to be a man! Let's see; don't tattle, always make fun of those different from you, never say anything unless you're sure everyone feels exactly the same way you do.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.06' title='Moaning Lisa'>
Bleeding Gums Murphy: The blues isn't about making yourself feeling better, it's about making other people feel worse.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.06' title='Moaning Lisa'>
Bleeding Gums Murphy: [to Lisa] You know, you play pretty well for someone with no real problems.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.07' title='The Call of the Simpsons'>
Lisa: Remember, Dad. The handle of the Big Dipper points to the North Star.
Homer: That's nice, Lisa, but we're not in astronomy class. We're in the woods. 
</quote>
<quote epno='1.08' title='THe Telltale Head'>
Homer: [on Heaven] I can understand how they wouldn't let in those wild jungle apes, but what about those really smart ones who live among us who roller-skate and smoke cigars?
</quote>
<quote epno='1.08' title='THe Telltale Head'>
Bart: Well, I was wondering... how important is it to be popular?
Homer: I'm glad you asked, son. Being popular is the most important thing in the world.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.11' title='The Crepes of Wrath'>
Marge: Deportation?! You mean kick Bart out of the country?!
Homer: Hear him out, Marge. 
</quote>
<quote epno='1.12' title='Krusty Gets Busted'>
"Krusty": Hand over all your money in a paper bag.
Apu: Yes, yes, I know the procedure for armed robbery. I do work in a convenience store, you know.
Apu: [to Homer] You can emerge now from my chips. The opportunity to prove yourself a hero is long gone.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.13' title='Some Enchanted Evening'>
Moe: [to Homer]See? You're a pig. Barney's a pig. Larry's a pig. We're all pigs. Except for one difference: once in a while, we can crawl out of the slop, hose ourselves off, and act like human beings.
</quote>
<quote epno='1.13' title='Some Enchanted Evening'>
Ms. Botz: You're a smart, young man, Bart! I hope you're smart enough to keep your mouth shut!
Lisa: He isn't.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Otto: Hey, Bart Dude. Woah, you look freaked!
Bart: Otto, man, I have a test today that I'm not ready for! Could you please crash the bus or something?
Otto: Sorry, Bart Dude. Can't do it on purpose. But hey, maybe you'll get lucky!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Bart: Say, who's up for a little cram session? I'll go first. What was the name of the Pilgrims' boat?
Sherri: The Spirit of St. Louis.
Bart: And where'd they land?
Terri: Sunny Acapulco.
Bart: And why'd they leave England?
Sherri: Giant rats.
Bart: [writing down the information in a notebook] Cool, history's coming alive!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Martin: As a natural enemy, I don't know why I should care. But the information you received regarding America's colonial period is erroneous.
Bart: Meaning....
Martin: A blindfolded chimp with a pencil in his teeth has a better chance of passing this test than you do!
Bart: Thanks for the pep talk...
</quote>
<quote epno='2.01' title='Bart Gets an F'>
Bart: Look at my eyes! See the sincerity? See the conviction? See the fear? As God is my witness, I can pass the fourth grade!
Homer: And if you don't, at least you'll be bigger than the other kids. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.02' title='Simpson and Delilah'>
Homer: D'oh! [stops strangling Bart] Dirty trick. Okay, I'm not going to kill you, but I'm going to tell you three things that are gonna haunt you for the rest of your days. You've ruined your father, you've crippled your family, and baldness is hereditary!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.03' title='Treehouse of Horror'>
Lisa: [reading] "Quit throwing your garbage into our dimension!"
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Mr. Burns: Ironic, isn't it Smithers. This anonymous clan of slack-jawed troglodytes has cost me the election, and yet if I were to have them killed, I would be the one to go to jail. That's democracy for you!
Smithers: You are noble and poetic in defeat, sir. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Barney Gumble: Oh no! An election! It's one of those deals where they close the bars isn't it?
</quote>
<quote epno='2.04' title='Two Cars in Every Garage and Three Eyes on Every Fish'>
Homer: Bart, would you like to say grace?
Bart: Dear God, we paid for all this stuff ourselves, so thanks for nothing. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Homer: For the first time in my life, people weren't laughing at me, they were laughing towards me!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Marge: A Simpson on a T-shirt, I thought I'd never see the day.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.05' title='Dancin Homer'>
Homer: I wonder why stories of degradation and humiliation make you more popular?
Moe: I don't know. They just do. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Homer: Marge, where's the Duff?!
Marge: Oh, uh, we're all out, Homer.
Homer: D'oh!
Marge: Would you like some fruit juice?
Homer: Don't toy with me, woman! 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Marge: Homer. I couldn't help overhearing you warp Bart's mind.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Lisa: Bart, having never received any words of encouragement myself I'm not sure how they're suppose to sound, but here it goes. I believe in you.
Bart: Thanks man. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.06' title='Dead Putting Society'>
Homer: C'mon Bart. Remember what Vince Lombarde said- "If you lose, you're out of the family."!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.07' title='Bart vs Thanksgiving'>
Grampa: Homer was never stubborn. he always folded instantly over anything. It was as if he had no will of his own. Isn't that true Homer?
Homer: Yes Dad. 
</quote>

<quote epno='2.07' title='Bart vs Thanksgiving'>
Grampa: Let's go. If I'm not back at the home by 9 they declare me legally dead and collect my insurance!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.08' title='Bart the Daredevil'>
Bart: Otto, I'm going to leap over Springfield Gorge on my skateboard.
Otto: You know, Bart, as the only adult here, I feel I should say something.
Bart: What?
Otto: COOOOOOOOL!!!!!
</quote>

<quote epno='2.08' title='Bart the Daredevil'>
Lance Murdock: It's always nice to see young people taking an interest in danger. Now, son, a lot of people are going to be telling you you're crazy - and maybe they're right! But I want to tell you three things: bones heal, chicks dig scars, and the United States of America has the best doctor-to-daredevil ratio in the world!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.10' title='Bart Gets Hit by a Car'>
Lionel Hutz: Hutz is the name, Mr. Simpson. Lionel Hutz, attorney-at-law. Here's my card. It turns into a sponge when you put it in water.
Homer: Ooh, classy.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.11' title='One Fish, Two Fish, Blowfish, Blue Fish'>
Dr. Hibbert: Now, a little death anxiety is normal. You can expect to go through five stages. The first is denial.
Homer: No way, because I'm not dying!
Dr. Hibbert: Second is anger.
Homer: [yelling] Why you little!
Dr. Hibbert: After that comes fear.
Homer: [worried] What's after fear? What's after fear?!
Dr. Hibbert: Bargaining.
Homer: Doc, you gotta get me outta this. I'll make it worth your while.
Dr. Hibbert: Finally acceptance.
Homer: Well, we all gotta go sometime.
Dr. Hibbert: Mr. Simpson, your progress astounds me.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Barney: Hey Homer! You're late for English!
Homer: English, who needs that? I'm never going to England. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Homer: [tries to ask Marge to the prom] Look, I'm not asking you to like me. I'm not asking you to put yourself in a position where I can touch your goodies. I'm just asking you to be fair.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.12' title='The Way We Was'>
Flashback Homer: Marge I have a problem. When you stop this car, I'm gonna hug you. And kiss you. And I'll never be able to let you go.
Present Homer: And I never have. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.13' title='Homer vs. Lisa and the 8th Commandment'>
Homer: [referring to Lisa] There's something wrong with that kid. She's so moral. Why can't she be more like...Well, not like Bart. But there has to be a happy medium. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.14' title='Principal Charming'>
Marge: It's Patty who chose a life of celibacy. Selma simply had celibacy thrust upon her.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.14' title='Principal Charming'>
Marge: You will find Selma a man!
Homer: All right.
Marge: And not just any man.
Homer: Okay!
Marge: He should be honest, and, and caring. And well-off. And handsome.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Bart: No way, she's faking! If Lisa stays home, I stay home.
Lisa: If Bart stays home, I'm going to school.
Bart: Fine, then... Wait a minute... If Lisa goes to school, then I go to school, but then Lisa stays home, so I stay home, so Lisa goes to school...
Marge: Lisa, don't confuse your brother like that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Mrs. Winthrop: Let me tell you the two most importand words you will ever hear in your life - "choke chain!"
</quote>
<quote epno='2.16' title='Barts Dog Gets an F'>
Martin: How can we tell if we're doing this maneuver effectively?
Mrs. Winthrop: The dog's eyes will bulge and his tongue will protrude and change color ever so slightly.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.17' title='Old Money'>
Marge: You know, we'll be old someday.
Homer: Gasp! My God, you're right, Marge! You kids wouldn't put me in a home like I did to my dad, would you?
Bart: Well...
Homer: Aaah! 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.17' title='Old Money'>
Grandpa:[asking a lady out on a date] Well, I was wondering if you and I you know, might go to the same place at the same time and... Jeez! You'd think this would get easier with time!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.18' title='Brush with Greatness'>
Burns: [offscreen] SMITHERS! I WANT MY TEA!
Marge: [to Smithers] Doesn't it bother you that he orders you around like that?
Smithers: [chuckles] Actually, I value every second we're together. From the moment I squeeze his orange juice in the morning, till I tuck him in at night. He's not just my boss, he's my best friend too. [Burns enters; Smithers gives him the tea]
Burns: [sipping] Bah! Too hot! [throws it on Smithers]
Smithers: Right, sir. It's... scalding me as we speak. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.19' title='Lisas Substitute'>
Mr. Bergstrom: Lisa, your homework is always so neat. How can I put this? Does your father help you with it?
Lisa: No. Homework's not my father's specialty.
Mr. Bergstrom: Well there's no shame in it, I mean, my dad--
Lisa: Not mine.
Mr. Bergstrom: You didn't let me finish--
Lisa: Unless the next word was "burped", you didn't have to. 
</quote>
<quote epno='2.19' title='Lisas Substitute'>
Homer: Hey! Just because I don't care doesn't mean I don't understand!
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Dr. Hibbert: [Homer is passed out on the floor as everyone leaves Marge's party.] If you want him to live through the night, I suggest you roll him onto his stomach.
Marge: Thank you, Doctor.
Dr. Hibbert: Remember, I said "if."
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Homer: About last night. You might have noticed Daddy acting a little strange and you probably don't understand why.
Bart: I understand why. You were wasted.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.20' title='The War of the Simpsons'>
Homer: I admit it. I didn't know when to say "when." I'm sorry it happened and I just hope you didn't lose a lot of respect for me.
Bart: Dad, I have as much respect for you as I ever did or ever will.
</quote>
<quote epno='2.22' title='Blood Feud'>
Marge: The moral of this story is a good deed is its own reward.
Bart: Hey, we got a reward. The head is cool!
Marge: Well then... I guess the moral is no good deed goes unrewarded.
Homer: Wait a minute! If I hadn't written that nasty letter, we wouldn't have gotten anything!
Marge: Well... then I guess the moral is the squeaky wheel gets the grease.
Lisa: Perhaps there is no moral to this story.
Homer: Exactly! It's just a bunch of stuff that happened.
Marge: But it certainly was a memorable few days.
Homer: Amen to that!
</quote>

<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Homer: Marge, I can't wear a pink shirt to work. Everyone wears white shirts. I'm not popular enough to be different.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Michael Jackson: I can't believe you've never heard of me, I'm a very popular entertainer.
Homer: of course I've heard of you! I mean you'd have to be living under a rock not to know...what'd you say you name was?
Michael Jackson: Michael Jackson.
Homer: Doesn't ring a bell.
Michael Jackson: Well have you heard of MTV?
Homer: No
Michael Jackson: Motown?
Homer: No
Michael Jackson: Beat it?
Homer: You beat it!
Michael Jackson: Thriller?
Homer: What was that last one again?
Michael Jackson: Thriller.
Homer: No. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Homer: Wow! How do you do that thing with your feet?
Michael Jackson: The moonwalk?
Homer: NO! That thing with your feet!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.01' title='Stark Raving Dad'>
Doctor: Mr. Simpson, after talking to your wife we believe you're no threat to yourself or others.
Homer: That's the most flattering thing anyone has ever said to me. Can I have it in writing? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: Who would've guessed reading and writing would pay off?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: Wow a shoehorn! Just like in the movies! Shoe goes on. Shoe goes off. Shoe goes on. Shoe goes off.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: I had a feeling it was too good to be true. Every time you get a million dollars, something queers the deal.
Lisa: I don't think real checks have exclamation points. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Homer: [reading] Then I heard the sound that all Arctic explorers dread... the pitiless bark of the sea lion! [gasp] He'll be killed!
Marge: Homer, he obviously got out alive if he wrote the article.
Homer: Don't be so... [flips ahead] Oh, you're right. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.02' title='Mr. Lisa Goes to Washington'>
Faith Crowley: And here are your V.I.P. badges. These will get into place regular tourists never get to see!
Homer: Oh, miss! What does the "I" stand for?
Faith Crowley: Um..."Important."
Homer: Oh, okay. What about the "V"?
Faith Crowley: "Very."
Homer: Miss, just one more qu...
Faith Crowley: "Person."
Homer: Uh-huh. [pause] What does the "I" stand for again? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.03' title='When Flander Failed'>
Homer: [On the phone] Hello, Jerry? Homer Simpson. Remember last month when I paid back that loan? Well now I need YOU to do a favor for ME.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.04' title='Bart the Murderer'>
Chief Wiggum: Fat Tony is a cancer on this fair city. And I am the... um... What cures cancer?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Kent Brockman: Uh, Mr. Burns, people are calling this a meltdown.
Mr. Burns: [over the hotline] Oh, meltdown. It's one of these annoying buzzwords. We prefer to call it an unrequested fission surplus. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Mr. Burns: Well Smithers, I guess there's nothing left to do but kiss my sorry ass good-bye.
Smithers: May I, sir?
Mr. Burns: Ewww... 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Apu: Oh Otto! Otto! Do you know there is a small child inside your bus?
Otto: Oh, good thing you warned me. I was on my way to Mexico. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.05' title='Homer Defined'>
Homer: Well ya know boys. A nuclear reactor's a lot like a woman. You just have to read the manual and press the right buttons.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.06' title='Like Father, Like Clown'>
Krusty: [voice-over] My father was the most respected person in the Lower East Side of Springfield. People would come for miles around to ask his advice.
Young Jewish Man: Reb Krustofsky, should I finish college?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Yes. No one is poor, except he who lacks knowledge.
Jewish Woman: Rabbi, should I have another child?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Yes. Another child would be a blessing on your house.
Jewish Man: Rabbi, should I buy a Chrysler?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Could you rephrase that as an ethical question?
Jewish Man: Um... is it right to buy a Chrysler?
Rabbi Hyman Krustofsky: Oh, yes! For great is the car with power steering and dyna-flow suspension. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.07' title='Treehouse of Horror II'>
Burns: [Burns transplants Homer's brain into a robot] Smithers, hand me that ice-cream scoop.
Smithers: Ice-cream scoop?!
Burns: Dammit, Smithers! This isn't rocket science, it's brain surgery!
Mister Burns: [Burns removes Homer's brain then puts it atop his own head] Look at me, I'm Davy Crockett!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Lisa: Dad, I broke my last saxophone reed, and I need you to get me a new one.
Homer: Uh, isn't this the kind of thing your mother's better at?
Lisa: I called her. She's not home. I also tried Mr. Flanders, Aunt Patty, Aunt Selma, Dr. Hibbert, Reverend Lovejoy, and that nice man who caught the snake in our basement.
Homer: Wow, and after them, out of all the people in the world, you chose me.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Marge: Hmmm, we're in serious trouble here. We're just going to have to cut back on luxuries.
Homer: Well, you know, we're always buying Maggie vaccinations for diseases she doesn't even have.
Marge: Actually, I was thinking we could cut back on your beer.
Homer: Nah, we're not gonna be doing that.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Marge: Alright, you got us into this, you get us out.
Homer: Fine! I will! There's plenty of money out there for a guy who's willing to work for it. [Pauses] You have any jewelry you don't need anymore? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Horse Trainer: Although there is no change in my patrician facade, I can assure you my heart is breaking. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.08' title='Lisas Pony'>
Bart: Hey, how come Lisa gets a pony!
Homer: Because she stopped loving me.
Bart: I don't love you either, so get me a moped.
Homer: I know you love me so you get squat. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.09' title='Saturdays of Thunder'>
Homer: You know, Marge, that Bart is a little miracle, his winning smile, his button nose, his fat little stomach, his face alight with wholesome mischief. He reminds me of me before the weight of the world crushed my spirit.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.09' title='Saturdays of Thunder'>
Homer's Brain: Don't you get it? You've got to use reverse psychology.
Homer: That sounds too complicated.
Homer's Brain: OK, don't use reverse psychology.
Homer: All right, I will! 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Moe: It's like there's a party in my mouth, and everyone's invited.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Homer: Moe, I haven't seen the place this crowded since the government cracked down on you for accepting food stamps.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.10' title='Flaming Moes'>
Miss Krabaple: Bart! Are those liquor bottles?
Bart: I brought enough for everbody.
Miss Krabaple: Take those to the teacher's lounge. You can have what's left at the end of the day 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Stockbroker: Homer, it's your stockbroker. Your stock in the powerplant just went up for the first time in 10 years.
Homer: I own stock!
Stockbroker: Yes, all the employees got some in exchange for waving certain constitutional rights. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Carl: Yeah, you know, those Germans aren't so bad.
Lenny: Sure they made mistakes in the past, but hey, that's why pencils have erasers! 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
German Managers: Attention workers, we have completed our evaluation of the plant. We regret to announce the following lay-offs, which I will read in alphabetical order... Simpson, Homer. That is all.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.11' title='Burns Verkaufen der Kraftwerk'>
Mr. Burns: What good is money if you can't inspire fear in your fellow man?
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Homer: Do you really think you're pregnant?
Marge: Well, I have the same nausea and craving for pancake mix I had with the other kids.
Homer: Yeah, and I have the same tightness in my chest and profuse sweating I always did. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Clerk: Basic ceremony's twenty bucks. Here's your license. [She hands them a punch card.] Be sure to get this punched every time. The tenth wedding is on the house!
Homer: Hey! This marriage is gonna last forever!
Clerk: [chuckling] No matter how many times I hear that, it still makes me laugh!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.12' title='I Married Marge'>
Homer: Marge, look at this! A baby monitor! [into the monitor] "Baby to Marge. Baby to Marge. Waa! Waa! Over."
Marge: Homer, I don't know how we can afford all these things on your salary. [Homer looks out the window and sees the Power Plant.]
Homer: Hey, why don't I apply at the Nuclear Power Plant. I hear they pay pretty well!
Marge: I don't know. I heard radiation can make you sterile.
Homer: Pfft. Now you tell me!
</quote>

<quote epno='3.13' title='Radio Bart'>
Kent: So, as it turns out, we've all been victims of a cruel hoax, masterminded by a 10-year old hooligan. The time has come for finger-pointing, and most of them are squarely aimed at the boy's parents.
Homer: It's not our fault! We didn't want the boy, he was an accident!
Marge: HOMER!
Homer: Sorry. Uh... could you edit that last part out?
Kent: Mr. Simpson, we're live, coast-to-coast.
Homer: D'oh!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.15' title='Homer Alone'>
Selma: Lisa, you'll sleep in my bed. Bart, you'll be sleeping with your Aunt Patty.
Bart: ...In your bed?
Patty: Uh-huh. And just a warning: I'm told I snore. [Patty and Selma chuckle. Bart and Lisa quickly grab each others hand]
Patty: Oh! "Divorce Court" is on in five minutes! [They get up and leave.]
Bart: I'm scared, Lisa.
Lisa: You think you know fear? Well, I've seen them naked! [Bart screams] 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.19' title='Dog of Death'>
Chief Wiggum: No, you got the wrong number. This is nine-one... two.
</quote>
<quote epno='3.19' title='Dog of Death'>
Smithers: People like dogs, Mr. Burns.
Burns: Nonsense! Dogs are idiots. Think about it, Smithers: if I came into your house and started sniffing at your crotch and slobbering all over your face, what would you say?
Smithers: [pause] If you did it, Sir? 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Redneck #1: Hey you! Let's fight!
Redneck #2: Them's fightin' words!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Studio Manager: You know, this studio has a lot of history. Buddy Holly stood on that same spot in 1955 and said, "There is no way in hell I am recording in this dump!"
</quote>
<quote epno='3.20' title='Colonel Homer'>
Marge: [after seeing Lurleen] I thought you said she was overweight.
Homer: Marge, it takes two to lie. One to lie, and one to listen. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.21' title='Black Widower'>
Marge: Now, now, he's an ex-convict! He's paid his debt to society!
Patty: Then how come you're not using the good silverware?
Marge: I'm just not. 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.22' title='The Otto Show'>
Marge: Why don't you go and live with your parents?
Otto: Oh, the admiral and I don't get along. Please let me stay here. I've got nowhere else to go!
Homer: Forget it. That line didn't work for my dad, and it's not gonna work for you.
Marge: Homer, I know we didn't ask for this, but doesn't the Bible say, "Whatever you do unto the least of these my brothers, that you do unto me?"
Homer: Yes, but doesn't the Bible also say, "Thou shalt not take moochers into thy...hut?" 
</quote>
<quote epno='3.22' title='The Otto Show'>
Bart: You can do it, Otto. You're the coolest adult I've ever met.
Otto: Wow! I've never been called an adult before. I've been tried as one, but... I'll do it!
</quote>
<quote epno='3.23' title='Barts Friend Falls in Love'>
Milhouse: Let me try. Will I get beat up today? [shakes the ball] "All Signs Point To Yes."
Nelson: That ball knows everything. [bashes Milhouse on the head.]
</quote>
<quote epno='3.24' title='Brother Cand You Spare Two Dimes?'>
Lisa: [At Homer's hastily-concocted award ceremony] This show is the biggest farce I ever saw!
Bart: What about the Emmys?
Lisa: I stand corrected.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.01' title='Kamp Krusty'>
Homer: Son. If you really want something in this life, you have to work for it. Quiet! They're gonna announce the lottery numbers. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.01' title='Kamp Krusty'>
Lisa: You're serving us gruel?
Dolph: Not quite. [pulls out a large drum of gruel with Krusty's face on the front] This is Krusty-Brand Imitation Gruel. Nine out of ten orphans can't tell the difference. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.03' title='Homer the Heretic'>
Marge: Homer, don't make me chose between my man and my God, because you just can't win.
Homer: There you are. Always taking someone else's side; Flanders, the water department, God... 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.03' title='Homer the Heretic'>
Homer: God?
God: [points finger at Homer] THOU HAST FORSAKEN MY CHURCH!
Homer: But Lord, I am not a bad man. I work hard and provide for the welfare of my family. So why should I be forced to spend half my Sunday listening about how I am going to Hell anyway?
God: You have a good point there. Sometimes, even I would rather be watching football. Does Saint Louis still have a team?
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Shopkeeper: Take this object, but beware it carries a terrible curse!
Homer: [worried] Ooooh, that's bad.
Shopkeeper: But it comes with a free Frogurt!
Homer: [relieved] That's good.
Shopkeeper: The Frogurt is also cursed.
Homer: [worried] That's bad.
Shopkeeper: But you get your choice of topping!
Homer: [relieved] That's good.
Shopkeeper: The toppings contains Potassium Benzoate.
Homer: [stares]
Shopkeeper: That's bad.
Homer: Can I go now?
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Mr. Burns: [about bringing Marge along on their voyage] What do you think, Smithers?
Smithers: I think women and seamen don't mix.
Mr. Burns: We know what you think. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.05' title='Treehouse of Horror III'>
Lisa: Thank God we didn't turn into a bunch of mindless zombies.
Bart: Shhh! TV! [The family stare blankly at the television. A thud is heard, followed by a laugh track.]
Homer: Man... fall down. Funny.
Family: Mmmmmm... 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.07' title='Marge Gets a Job'>
Smithers: This resume is very impressive. Let me be the first to say Abibu gazini.
Marge: What?
Smithers: "Welcome aboard." I guess my Swahili's not as good as yours. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.08' title='New Kid on the Block'>
Homer: [to Bart and Lisa] SHUT UP, YOU LITTLE MONSTERS! [to the phone] I was wondering if you'd like to babysit my little angels. [On the other end of the line...]
Woman: I'm sorry, this isn't Abby. This is her sister. I look after her now. [Abby rocks in her chair and mumbles quietly to herself.]
Abby: No, Bart... put it down... put it down, Bart... put it down...
</quote>
<quote epno='4.08' title='New Kid on the Block'>
Homer: You see, son, a woman is a lot like... err... a refrigerator! They're about six feet tall, 300 pounds... they... make ice... uhhh... oh! Actually, a woman is more like a beer. They smell good, they look good, you'd step over your own mother just to get one! [drains his beer] But you can't stop at one, you wanna drink another woman! [runs to the fridge]
</quote>
<quote epno='4.11' title='Homers Triple Bypass'>
Bart: Nothing you say can upset us. We're the MTV generation.
Lisa: We feel neither highs or lows.
Homer: Really? What's it like?
Lisa: Meh. [shrugs]. 
</quote>

<quote epno='4.11' title='Homers Triple Bypass'>
Homer: Don't worry Marge. America's health care system is second only to Japan... Canada, Sweden, Great Britain... well, all of Europe. But you can thank your lucky stars we don't live in Paraguay!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.12' title='Marge vs. the Monorail'>
Marge: How fast are they going?
Homer: Eeeeeyaaaaaaai! [super fast as monorail whizzes by platform]
Cobb: [looking at watch] Well, judging by your husband's cowardly scream, a hundred eighty miles an hour. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.13' title='Selmas Choice'>
Bart and Homer: [singing] On top of spaghetti all covered with cheese, I lost my poor meatball...
Marge: If you don't mind, we're on our way to a funeral!
Homer: Ding dong the witch is dead...
Bart: Which Old Witch?
Homer: The Wicked Witch! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.15' title='I Love Lisa'>
Ralph: Dad, how do you get a girl to like you?
Chief Wiggum: Son, [cracks a nut with the butt of his revolver] whether you want to win a girl or crack a nut, the key is persistence; [cracks a nut] keep at it, and never lose your cool. Chief Wiggum tries to crack a third nut, but the shell doesn't break.]
Chief Wiggum: [losing patience] Ah, come on, you stupid...! [Chief Wiggum loads his gun up and shoots the nut.]
Chief Wiggum: [angrily] Let that be a lesson to the rest of you... nuts!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.15' title='I Love Lisa'>
Homer: Is there a problem, officer?
Chief Wiggum: Yep. Got a tail-light out.
Homer: Where?!
Chief Wiggum: [Smashing a tail-light] Right there.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.16' title='Duffless'>
Otto: My name is Ot-to. I love to get blot-to!
Hans Moleman: My name is Hans. Drinking has ruined my life. I'm 31 years old!
Homer: My name is Homer and I'm just here because the Court made me come.
Lovejoy: Homer, with our help you'll never touch a beer again. [Homer screams and jumps through the window]
</quote>
<quote epno='4.17' title='Last Exit to Springfield'>
Factory Worker: You can't treat the working man this way! One day, we'll form a union and get the fair and equitable treatment we deserve! Then we'll go too far, and get corrupt and shiftless, and the Japanese will eat us alive!
Burns's Grandfather: The Japanese? Those sandal-wearing goldfish-tenders? Bosh! Flimshaw!
Mr. Burns: [to Smithers, in the present] If only we'd listened to that boy, instead of walling him up in the abandoned coke oven. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.18' title='So Its Come to This: A Simpsons Clip Show'>
Lou: That sounded like an explosion at the old Simpson place.
Chief Wiggum: Forget it. That's two blocks away.
Lou: Looks like there's beer coming out of the chimney. [Wiggum gets out of the car]
Chief Wiggum: I am proceeding on foot. Call in a Code 8.
Lou: [into radio] We need pretzels. Repeat, pretzels.
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Bart: Hey Grampa, we need to know your first name.
Grampa Simpson: [gasps in horror] YOU'RE MAKING MY TOMBSTONE! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Lisa: [to Grampa] So, we wrote the cartoon, put your name on it and sent it in.
Bart: Didn't you wonder why you were getting checks for doing absolutely nothing?
Grampa: I figured, cause the Democrats were in power again. 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.19' title='The Front'>
Bart: Hey Grampa, we need to know your first name.
Grampa Simpson: [gasps in horror] YOU'RE MAKING MY TOMBSTONE! 
</quote>
<quote epno='4.21' title='Marge in Chains'>
Ned: Oh, the network slogan is true! Watch Fox and be damned for all eternity!
</quote>
<quote epno='4.21' title='Marge in Chains'>
Hutz: Your Honor, my client claims that she simply forgot she was carrying this bottle of... delicious bourbon... brownest of the brown liquors... so tempting... [puts the bottle to his ear] What's that? You want me to drink you? But I'm in the middle of a trial! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Marge: Lisa, you got a letter.
Lisa: It's from my pen pal, Anya! [As Lisa reads, the letter writer's voice can be heard in voice over.]
Anya: "Dear Lisa - as I write this, I am very sad. Our president has been overthrown and...
Gruff male voice: ...replaced by the benevolent General Krull. All hail Krull and his glorious new regime! Sincerely, Little Girl." 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Chief Wigggum: I'd like to help you ma'am, but, heh heh, I'm afraid there's no law against mailing threatening letters.
Marge: [indignantly] I'm pretty sure there is!
Wiggum: Hah! The day I take cop lessons from Ma Kettle...
Lou: Hey, she's right, Chief.[Lou shows Chief Wiggum a book called "Springfield Law"]
</quote>
<quote epno='5.02' title='Cape Feare'>
Wiggum: Well, shut my mouth. It's also illegal to put squirrels down your pants for the purposes of gambling. [Cut to Eddie with squirrels in his pants while the other cops watch and laugh, rolling dice]
Wiggum: Boys, knock it off!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.03' title='Homer Goes to College'>
Smithers: [The plant melting down, Mr. Burns gets into escape pod and shuts Smithers out.] For the love of God, sir, there are two seats!
Burns: I like to put my feet up.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.06' title='Marge on the Lam'>
Rescue Worker: Homer, there's no easy way to put this, but we're going to have to saw your arms off.
Homer: They'll grow back, right?
Rescue Worker: Oh... yeah.
Homer: Whew. 
</quote>

<quote epno='5.07' title='Barts Inner Child'>
Troy McClure: Hi! I'm Troy McClure! You might remember me from such self-help videos as 'Smoke Yourself Thin' and 'Get Confident, Stupid!'
</quote>
<quote epno='5.08' title='Boy-Scoutz N the Hood'>
Homer: Marge, don't discourage the boy. Weaseling out of things is important to learn. It's what separates us from the animals! Except the weasel.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.09' title='THe Last Temtation of Homer'>
Charlie: [explaining about the gas leak] Well, sir, I won't bore you with the details of our miraculous escape, but we desperately need a real emergency exit!
Burns: Why, that's a fabulous idea. Anything else you'd like? How about real lead in the radiation shields? Urinal cakes, maybe? [hands Smithers a notebook] Smithers, throw this at him! [Smithers throws the book at Charlie, and Burns presses a button. A tube covers Charlie and sucks him upwards]
</quote>
<quote epno='5.10' title='$pringfield [Or, How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling'>
Kent Brockman: Scott, things aren't as happy as they used to be down here at the Unemployment Office, joblessness is no longer just for philosophy majors... now at the risk of sounding unpopular, this reporter places the blame for all of this squarely on you [pointing at the camera] the viewers!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.10' title='$pringfield [Or, How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling'>
Lisa: Dad! You shouldn't wear glasses that weren't prescribed for you!
Homer: [looking at Bart] Lisa just because you're ten feet tall doesn't mean you can tell me what to do. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.11' title='Homer the Vigilante'>
Kent Brockman: Hordes of panicky people seem to be evacuating the town for some unknown reason. Professor, without knowing precisely what the danger is, would you say it's time for our viewers to crack each other's heads open and feast on the goo inside?
Professor: Mmm, yes I would, Kent. 
</quote>

<quote epno='5.12' title='Bart Gets Famous'>
Bart: [after Marge has convinced  him to peform one more time] You're right, Mom. I shouldn't let this bother me. I'm in television now. It's my job to be repetitive. My job. My job. Repetitiveness is my job. [To Marge] I'm gonna go out there and give the best performance of my life!
Marge: The best performance of your life?
Bart: The best performance of my life!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.12' title='Bart Gets Famous'>
Lisa: And now you can go back to just being you, instead of a one-dimensional character with a silly catch-phrase.
Homer: [breaking a lamp] D'oh!
Bart: Ay, caramba!
Marge: [groans]
Maggie: [sucks her pacifier]
Flanders: Hi-dilly-ho!
Barney: [belches]
Nelson: Ha, ha!
Burns: Excellent!
Lisa: [Long pause. Everyone looks expectantly at Lisa.] If anyone wants me, I'll be in my room.
Homer: What kind of catch phrase is that!? 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.13' title='Homer and Apu'>
Homer: Your old meat made me sick!
Apu: Oh I am so sorry. Please accept five pounds of frozen shrimp as an apology.
Homer: This shrimp isn't frozen! And it smells funny!
Apu: Okay, ten pounds.
Homer: Woo-hoo! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.13' title='Homer and Apu'>
Homer: Life is just one crushing defeat after another until you just wish that Flanders was dead.        
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Malibu Stacy Doll: Don't ask me. I'm just a girl! Tee-hee!
Bart: Right on! Say it, sister!
Lisa: This isn't funny, Bart! Millions of girls will grow up thinking that this is the right way to act - that they can never be more than vacuous ninnies whose only goal in life is to look pretty, land a rich husband and spend all day on the phone with their equally vacuous friends and talk about how damned terrific it is to look pretty and have a rich husband!
Bart:...Just what I was gonna say! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Mr. Burns: [Smithers turns his computer on. A bitmapped Mr. Burns [shown naked from the shoulders up] appears] [in stilted speech] Hello, Smithers. You're quite good at tur-ning me-on.
Smithers: [to Lisa] Um... you probably should ignore that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.14' title='Lisa vs. Malibu Stacy'>
Stacy: I see exactly what you mean; this is a problem. But what do you expect me to do?
Lisa: Change what she says. It's your company.
Stacy: Not since I was forced out in 1974. They said my way of thinking just wasn't cost effective.
Lisa: [gasps] That's awful.
Stacy: Well, that - and I was funneling profits to the Viet Cong.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.15' title='Deep Space Homer'>
Stillwater: People, we're in danger of losing our funding. America isn't interested in space exploration anymore.
Babcock: Maybe we should finally tell them the big secret, that all the chimps we sent into space came back super intelligent. [A chair swivels around, revealing a chimp in a suit, wearing glasses, and smoking a pipe.]
Chimp: [arrogant; English accent] No, I don't think we'll be telling them that. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.15' title='Deep Space Homer'>
Reporter: Uh, question for the barbecue chef: Don't you think there is an inherent danger in sending underqualified civilians into space?
Homer: I'll field this one. The only danger is if they send us to that terrible Planet of the Apes. [Homer thinks for a moment and realises something.]
Homer: Wait a minute, Statue of Liberty - that was our planet! You maniacs! You blew it up! Damn you! Damn you all to hell! 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.16' title='Homer Loves Flanders'>
Mr. Burns: [Mr. Burns talking to football players before the game] Men, there's a little crippled boy sitting in a hospital who wants you to win this game. I know because.. I crippled him myself to inspire you. [cuts to Milhouse lying in a hospital bed with a broken leg and his parents at his sid]
Milhouse: I hope they win or Mr. Burns said he's coming back. [Kirk and Luann look at each other worried] 
</quote>

<quote epno='5.17' title='Bart Gets an Elephant'>
Lisa: Wanna come with me, Daddy-o?
Homer: Sorry, honey. I'd love to, but Daddy has to go to a beer-drinking contest.
Bart: Think you'll win?
Homer: Son, when you participate in sporting events, it's not whether you win or lose; it's how drunk you get.
</quote>    
<quote epno='5.17' title='Bart Gets an Elephant'>
Lisa: Dad, you can't sell Stampy to him, I'm pretty sure he's an ivory dealer, his boots are ivory, his hat is ivory, his pen is ivory and I'm pretty sure that check is ivory!
Homer: Lisa, a guy who's got lots of ivory is less likely to hurt Stampy than a guy whose ivory supplies are low. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.17' title='Bart Gets an Elephant'>
Lisa: Sir, are you an ivory dealer?
Mr. Blackheart: Little girl, I have had many jobs throughout my life. Whale hunter, seal clubber, president of the Fox network. And like all men, yes, I have dealt a little ivory. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.18' title='Burns Heir'>
Smithers: Oh my God, Mr. Burns is dead! [Starts crying] Why do the good have to die so young?
</quote>
<quote epno='5.18' title='Burns Heir'>
Homer: Or what? You'll release the dogs, or the bees, or the dogs with bees in their mouths and when they bark they shoot bees at you?
</quote>
<quote epno='5.19' title='Sweet Seymour Skinners Badassss Song'>
Chalmers: Seymour, you're fired.
Skinner: Did you just call me a liar?
Chalmers: No, I said you were fired.
Skinner: Oh. That's much worse. 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.19' title='Sweet Seymour Skinners Badassss Song'>
Bart: Come on, Chalmie, you fired Skinner for less than this.
Chalmers: Yeah, I did, but... Skinner really bugged me! Besides, the way America's public schools are sliding, they'll all be this way in a few months. I say, lay back and enjoy it! It's a hell of a toboggan ride.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.19' title='Sweet Seymour Skinners Badassss Song'>
Ned: [over PA] Well, cockly-doodly-doo, little buddies. Let's thank the Lord for another beautiful school day.
Chalmers: Thank the Lor - thank the Lord? That sounded like a prayer. A prayer. A prayer in a public school! God has no place within these walls, just like facts have no place within organized religion. Simpson, you get your wish: Flanders is history!
</quote>
<quote epno='5.20' title='The Boy Who Knew Too Much'>
Skinner: You're stealing a table?
Homer: I'm not stealing it. Hotels expect you to take a few things. It's a souvenir!
Skinner: Ah... Is that my necktie you're wearing?
Homer: Souvenir.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.20' title='The Boy Who Knew Too Much'>
Bart: Mom, what if there's a really bad, crummy guy who's going to jail, but I know he's innocent?
Marge: Well Bart, your Uncle Arthur used to have a saying: "Shoot 'em all and let God sort them out." Unfortunately, one day he put his theory into practice. It took seventy-five Federal Marshals to bring him down. Now let's never speak of this again.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.21' title='Lady Bouviers Lover'>
Marge: Homer! You didn't do a very good job frosting Maggie's birthday cake!
[The cake reads, "Happy Birthday Magaggie."]
Homer: What? It's not Magaggie's birthday? 
</quote>
<quote epno='5.22' title='Secrets of a Successful Marriage'>
Homer: Oh... and how is education supposed to make me feel smarter? Besides, every time I learn something new, it pushes some old stuff out of my brain. Remember when I took that home wine-making course and I forgot how to drive?
Marge: That's because you were drunk.
Homer: And how.
</quote>
<quote epno='5.22' title='Secrets of a Successful Marriage'>
Rev. Lovejoy: Get a divorce.
Helen Lovejoy: Mmm-hmm.
Marge: But isn't that a sin?
Rev. Lovejoy: Marge, just about everything is a sin. [Holds up a Bible] You ever sat down and read this thing? Technically, we're not allowed to go to the bathroom.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.01' title='Bart of Darkness'>
Bart: This can't be what it looks like. There's gotta be some other explanation!
Ned Flanders: I wish there was some other explanation for this. But there isn't. I'm a murderer, I'm a murderer!
Bart: Then that's not the real Ned Flanders.
Ned Flanders: I'm a mur-diddly-urdler!
Bart: If that's not Flanders, he's done his homework.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.01' title='Bart of Darkness'>
Automated phone: Hello, and welcome to the Springfield Police Department "Rescue Phone"! If you know the name of the felony being committed, press one. To choose from a list of felonies, press two. If you are being murdered, or are calling from a rotary phone, please stay on the line.
[Bart presses four numbers on the phone]
Automated phone: You have selected "regicide!" If you know the name of the King or Queen being murdered, press one.
[Bart hangs up] 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.02' title='Lisas Rival'>
Homer: [spoken with strong Cuban accent] In America, first you get the sugar, then you get the power, then you get the women. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.02' title='Lisas Rival'>
Homer: And you said I wouldn't make any money! I found a dollar while waiting for the bus!
Marge: While you were out "earning" that dollar, you lost $80 by not going into work today. The plant called and said if you don't come in tomorrow, don't bother coming in Monday.
Homer: Woo-hoo! Four-day weekend! 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.02' title='Lisas Rival'>
Marge: Homer, when are you going to give up this crazy sugar scheme?
Homer: Never, Marge. Never. I can't live the button-down life like you. I want it all: the terrifying lows, the dizzying highs, the creamy middles. Sure, I might offend a few of the bluenoses with my cocky stride and musky odors -- oh, I'll never be the darling of the so-called ‘City Fathers’ who cluck their tongues, stroke their beards, and talk about "What's to be done with this Homer Simpson?" 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.03' title='Another Simpsons Clip Show'>
Marge: How many times can you laugh at that cat getting hit by the moon?
Bart: It's a new episode.
Lisa: Not exactly. They pieced it together from old shows, but it seems new to the trusting eyes of impressionable youth.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.03' title='Another Simpsons Clip Show'>
Lisa: Mom, romance is dead. It was acquired by Hallmark and Disney in a hostile takeover, homogenized, and sold off piece by piece.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.04' title='Itchy and Scratchy Land'>
Lisa: Dad! Remember when we asked you if we could go to Itchy and Scratchy Land and you said it'd be too damned expensive?
Homer: Oh, everything's too damned expensive these days. Look at this Bible I just bought, fifteen bucks! And talk about a preachy book, everyone's a sinner. Except for this guy. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.04' title='Itchy and Scratchy Land'>
Announcer: Attention Marge Simpson, we have arrested your son. Attention Marge Simpson, we have also arrested your older, fatter, balder son.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.05' title='Sideshow Bob Roberts'>
Sideshow Bob: I'm in jail for a crime I didn't even commit. Ha! "Attempted murder?" I mean, what is that? Do they give out a Nobel Prize for "attempted chemistry"? [someone throws a toilet that nearly hits Bob] Oh, really now! This is a personal call!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.05' title='Sideshow Bob Roberts'>
Sideshow Bob: [after Bart upstages him at a speech] That was a big mistake, Bart. No children have ever crossed the Republican Party and lived to tell about it!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.06' title='Barts Girlfriend'>
Bart's Brain: Now, just relax. For once, you didn't do anything wrong. Just explain yourself and everyone will understand.
Bart: I --
Helen Lovejoy: -- took the money? Yes, we know.
Moe: He confessed!
Bart: O-K!    [Jumps out the window] 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.06' title='Barts Girlfriend'>
Marge: I guess we could get more involved in Bart's activities but then I'd be afraid of smothering him.
Homer: Yeah, and then we'd get the chair.
Marge: That's not what I meant.
Homer: It was, Marge, admit it.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.08' title='Lisa on Ice'>
Homer: Lisa, if the Bible has taught us nothing else - and it hasn't - it's that girls should stick to girls' sports, such as hot-oil wrestling, foxy boxing, and such-and-such.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.08' title='Lisa on Ice'>
Homer: [Bart scores a goal] I love Bart!
Homer: [Lisa blocks Bart's shot] I mean, I love Lisa!
Homer: [Marge arrives with a tray of beers] Beer! Oh, Marge, I love you! 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.09' title='Homer: Bad Man'>
TV announcer: "Tonight on FOX, Homer Simpson, Portrait of an Assgrabber," starring Dennis Franz.
Homer: Ooh, "Portrait," sounds classy!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.09' title='Homer: Bad Man'>
Ashley: No, Mr. Simpson! A cat is a living creature!
Dennis Franz as Homer: I don't care! [He hits the cat, who screeches loudly. He stops the car and eyes Ashley lustfully.]'
Dennis Franz as Homer: Now I'm gonna grab me some sweet!
Ashley: Mr. Simpson, that's sexual harassment! If you keep it up, I'll scream so loud the whole country will hear!
Dennis Franz as Homer: With a man in the White House? Not likely! Scream as loud as you want, baby!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.09' title='Homer: Bad Man'>
Homer: Marge, kids. everything's gonna be just fine. Now go up stairs pack your bags, we're gonna start a new life... under the sea. [sighs] [Fantasy based on the "Under the Sea" number from "The Little Mermaid."]
Homer: [singing] Under the sea! Under the sea! [eats three fish] there'll be no accusations, just friendly crustaceans under the sea! [Seahorses swim inside his mouth. Homer then eats a lobster, two dancing slugs, a snail. He ends the fantasy surrounded by several fish skeletons. Back to reality...]
Marge: Homer, that's your solution to everything: move under the sea. It's not gonna happen!
Homer: Not with that attitude! 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.10' title='Grampa vs. Sexual Inadequacy'>
Lisa: I found the new Al Gore book.
Marge: "Sane Planning, Sensible Tomorrow."
Lisa: Yeah, I hope it's as exciting as his other book, "Rational Thinking, Reasonable Future". 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.10' title='Grampa vs. Sexual Inadequacy'>
Grampa: Here you go, ya ingrate! Think of me when you're havin' the best sex of your life!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.11' title='Fear of Flying'>
Homer: The last bar in Springfield. If they don't let me in here, I'm gonna have to quit drinking.
Homer's Liver: Yay!
Homer: Shut up, liver! [Homer punches his liver]
Homer: Ow! My liver hurts!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.11' title='Fear of Flying'>
Airport Worker: We need a pilot, pronto! Who wants to fly to the Windy City? [all of the pilots stand up, trying to get his attention]
Airport Worker: Conditions are a little windy! [all of the pilots who stood up sit down, leaving Homer standing]
Airport Worker: You! [points at Homer]
Homer: Me? But I...
Airport Worker: Hey! You're not just impersonating a pilot so you can drink here, are you?
Homer: Yeah. That's exactly why I'm here.
Airport Worker: [laughs] You flyboys, you crack me up! [cuts to the cockpit of a plane]
Homer: But I keep telling you, I'm not a pilot!
Airport Worker: And I keep telling you, you flyboys crack me up! [forces Homer into room] 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.11' title='Fear of Flying'>
Marge: Everyone has a fear of something.
Homer: Not everybody.
Marge: Sockpuppets!
Homer: WHERE, WHERE?!! AAAHH! AAAAHHHH!! [runs away]
</quote>
<quote epno='6.12' title='Homer the Great'>
Homer: I've always wondered if there was a god. And now I know there is -- and it's me.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.12' title='Homer the Great'>
Homer: They looked deep into my soul, and assigned me a number based on the order in which I joined!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.13' title='And Maggie Makes Three'>
Mr. Burns: [Homer quits the power plant, grabbing Mr. Burns and playing his bald head like a bongo drum.] I should be resisting this, but I'm paralyzed with rage... and island rhythms. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.13' title='And Maggie Makes Three'>
At the hospital, Mayor Quimby holds a newborn child in his arms while the mother [a young woman] rests.
Quimby: [Mayor Quimby holds a newborn child in his arms while the mother [a young woman] rests.] This is incredible. It's God's most wondrous miracle.
Nurse: Sir, I think your wife wants to hold the baby.
Quimby: My wife? Where? Where?! [runs off in a panic] 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.13' title='And Maggie Makes Three'>
Homer:[Homer holds Maggie for the first time.] Awww, it's a boy! [Looking down] And what a boy!
Dr. Hibbert: Mr. Simpson, that's the umbilical cord. It's a girl!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.14' title='Barts Comet'>
Arnie: With our utter annihilation imminent, our federal government has snapped into action. We go live now via satellite to the floor of the United States congress.
Speaker: Then it is unanimous, we are going to approve the bill to evacuate the town of Springfield in the great state of-
Congressman: Wait a second, I want to tack on a rider to that bill - $30 million of taxpayer money to support the perverted arts.
Speaker: All in favor of the amended Springfield-slash-pervert bill?
[entire congress boos]
Speaker: Bill defeated!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.14' title='Barts Comet'>
Kent Brockman: I've said it before and I'll say it again: democracy simply doesn't work.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.14' title='Barts Comet'>
Lisa: I can't believe that extra-thick layer of pollution that I've actually picketed against burned up the comet.
Bart: But what's really amazing is that this is exactly what dad said would happen.
Lisa: Yeah, dad was right.
Homer: I know, kids. I'm scared too!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.15' title='Homie the Clown'>
Lisa: When Krusty wants to, he can still blow 'em away!
Bart: He can take a simple, every day thing like eating a bicycle, and make it funny.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.15' title='Homie the Clown'>
Homer: But wait, you can't kill me for being Krusty. I'm not him! I'm Homer Simpson!
Fat Tony: The same Homer Simpson who crashed his car through our club?
Homer: Uh... actually my name is Barney. Yeah, Barney Gumble!
Legs: The same Barney Gumble who keeps taking pictures of my sister?
Homer: Uh... actually my real name is uh... think Krusty, think... Joe Valachi!
Louie: The same Joe Valachi who squealed to the Senate Committee about organized crime?
Homer: Benedict Arnold!
Fat Tony: The same Benedict Arnold who plotted to surrender West Point to the hated British?
Homer: D'oh!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.16' title='Bart vs. Australia'>
Australian man: You call that a knife? This is a knife!
Bart: That's not a knife. That's a spoon.
Australian man: All right, all right, you win. Heh. I see you've played knifey-spooney before. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.16' title='Bart vs. Australia'>
Bart: Hey, G.I.Joe: your sign's broken. We're already in Australia.
Marine: Actually, Sir, the embassy is considered American soil, Sir!
Homer: Really? Look, boy, now I'm in Australia...[hops over the line]...Now I'm in America...Australia! America!
Bart: I get it, Dad.
Homer: Australia! America!
Marge: Homer, that's enough!
Homer: Australia! America!
[The Marine decks Homer, knocking him down.]
Marine: Here in America, we don't tolerate that kind of crap, Sir!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.17' title='Homer vs. Patty and Selma'>
Stockbroker: Homer, you knuckle-beak! I told you a hundred times to sell your pumpkin futures before Halloween! Before!
Homer: All right, let's not panic. I'll make the money back by selling one of my livers. I can get by with one! 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.17' title='Homer vs. Patty and Selma'>
Patty: When are you going to wake up and smell your husband, Marge?
Selma: Granted, you got some kids out of him. But when the seeds have been planted, you throw away the envelope!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.18' title='A Star is Burns'>
Woman: [Two women are watching Barney's film about his alcoholism.] It's brilliant. Savagely honest, tender, he has the soul of a poet.
Barney: You're very kind.
Woman: Excuse me, did something crawl down your throat and die?
Barney: It didn't die! 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.18' title='A Star is Burns'>
Barney: My name's Barney, and I'm an alcoholic. [Camera pulls out to reveal that Barney is surrounded by little girls in scout uniforms, one of whom is Lisa.]
Lisa: Mr. Gumble, this is a Girl Scout meeting.
Barney: Is it, or is it that you girls can't admit you have a problem?
</quote>
<quote epno='6.19' title='Lisas Wedding'>
Marge: Remember, in England, an elevator is called a lift, a mile is called a kilometer, and botulism is called steak and kidney pie.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.19' title='Lisas Wedding'>
Homer: I've got to call everyone and tell them the good news! [picks up the receiver, but gets a busy signal] What the... ? Maggie, I need to use the phone! [upstairs, Maggie rolls her eyes and hangs up] Doesn't that girl ever shut up?
</quote>
<quote epno='6.20' title='Two Dozen and one greyhounds'>
Homer: Aww, so that's wrong with the poor fella. He misses casual sex!
</quote>
<quote epno='' title=''>
Mr. Burns: [singing to the tune of that song i forgot the name of]
Mr. Burns: Some men hunt for sport
Mr. Burns: others hunt for food
Mr. Burns: The only thing I'm hunting for...
Mr. Burns: is an outfit that looks good
Mr. Burns: See my vest, see my vest
Mr. Burns: made from real gorilla chest
Mr. Burns: See this sweater? There's no better
Mr. Burns: than authentic Irish Setter
Mr. Burns: See this hat? 'Twas my cat
Mr. Burns: My evening wear vampire bat
Mr. Burns: These white slippers are albino
Mr. Burns: african endangered rhino
Mr. Burns: Grizzle-bear underwear
Mr. Burns: turtle's necks I've got my share
Mr. Burns: Beret of poodle on my noodle it shall rest
Mr. Burns: Try my red robin suit
Mr. Burns: It comes one breast or two
Mr. Burns: See my vest, see my vest
Mr. Burns: See my vest!!
Mr. Burns: Like my loafers? Former gophers
Mr. Burns: It was that or skin my chauffeurs
Mr. Burns: But a greyhound-fur tuxedo would be best
Mr. Burns: So, let's prepare these dogs
Old Woman: Kill two for matching clogs!
Mr. Burns: See my vest... See my vest!
Mr. Burns: Oh please, won't you see my vest!!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.21' title='The PTA Disbands!'>
Bart: Krabappel said you would give the teachers anything they wanted.
Principal Skinner: She did?
Bart: Yeah. She said you would fold faster than Superman on laundry day. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.21' title='The PTA Disbands!'>
Homer: Lousy teachers, trying to pawn off our kids on us!
Lisa: But, Dad, by striking they're trying to effect a change in management so that they can be happier and more productive.
Homer: Lisa, if you don't like your job you don't strike: you just go in every day and do it really half-assed. That's the American way. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.22' title='Round Springfield'>
Bart: [in the nurse's office] Lunchlady Doris? What are you doing here?
Lunchlady Doris: Budget cuts. They've even got Groundskeeper Willie teaching French. [Cut to Groundskeeper Willie in French class with a beret on.]
Groundskeeper Willie: Bun-jerrr, you cheese-eatin' surrender monkeys!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.22' title='Round Springfield'>
Lisa:[Lisa finds a copy of "Sax on the Beach" at the comic book store. It's $250.] Two-hundred and fifty dollars? But I need that record to honor Bleeding Gums's memory!
Comic Book Guy: He's dead? Well why didn't you say so? [Comic Book Guy marks out the $250 price tag and writes $500 in its place.]
</quote>
<quote epno='6.23' title='The Springfield Connection'>
Homer: When Marge first told me she was going to the police academy, I thought it'd be fun and exciting, you know, like that movie... Spaceballs. But instead it's been painful and disturbing like that movie Police Academy.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.23' title='The Springfield Connection'>
Chief Wiggum:  [Marge is on the shooting range shooting cardboard cutouts of criminals and not shooting at civilians] You missed the baby, the blind guy... 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.24' title='Lemon of Troy'>
Database: Uh-oh, the trail has become indistinct. I suggest we split up to cover more ground.
Bart: Good idea. Milhouse, you and me will be Omega Team. Todd, you and Data are Team Strike Force. Nelson, that leaves you and Martin.
Martin: Team Discovery Channel!
Nelson: [groaning] Oh...your wussiness better come in handy. 
</quote>
<quote epno='6.24' title='Lemon of Troy'>
Bart: That tree is a part of our history and, as kids, the backbone of our economy! We'll get it back or choke their rivers with our dead!!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.25' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part One]'>
Mr. Burns: [Mr. Burns laughs evilly to himself and stomps through a scale model of Springfield like a giant monster.] Take that, Bowlarama! Take that, Convinience Mart! Take that, Nuclear Power Pl......oh, fiddlesticks!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.25' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part One]'>
Mr. Burns: Since the beginning of time, man has yearned to destroy the sun. I will do the next best thing: block it out! [He presses yet another button, raising a shield over the model town which blots out the sunlight.]
Smithers: [horrified] Good God!
Mr. Burns: Imagine it, Smithers: electrical lights and heaters running all day long!
</quote>
<quote epno='6.25' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part One]'>
Mayor Quimby: People, take it easy! We're all upset about Mr. Burns plan to block out our sun. It is time for decisive action. I have here a polite but firm letter to Mr. Burns' underlings who in some conjoin will pass it along to him or at least give him the jist of it.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.25' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part One]'>
Smithers [sounding and looking drunk] Mr. Burns was the closest thing I ever had...a friend. But he fired me! And now I spend my days drinking cheap Scotch and watching Comedy Central.
</quote>
<quote epno='6.25' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part One]'>
Mr. Burns: One last question. Have you ever seen the sun set at 3 p.m.
Captain McAllister: Aye, once. When I was sailing round the artic...
Mr. Burns: [interrupts] Shut up, you! Take one last look at the sun, Springfield! [pushes a button on a remote devices that activates his sun-blocker machine]
</quote>
<quote epno='7.01' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part Two]'>
Smithers: [Smithers sits in a confessional] Father, I'm not a Catholic. I tried to march in the St. Patrick's day parade but... anyway, I've got a rather large sin to confess. I'm the one who... [breaks down sobbing] Who shot Mr. Burns!
Chief Wiggum: [Chief Wiggum opens the screen and cocks his pistol] That's all I needed to hear. Boy, this thing works great. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.01' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part Two]'>
Eddie: Do you hold a grudge against Montgomery Burns?
Moe: No. [lie detector buzzez, red light] All right, maybe I did. But I didn't shoot him! [ding, green light]
Eddie: Checks out. Okay, sir, you're free to go.
Moe: Good, 'cause I got a hot date tonight. [buzz] A date. [buzz] Dinner with friends. [buzz] Dinner alone. [buzz] Watching TV alone. [buzz] All right! I'm going to sit at home and ogle the ladies in the Victoria's Secret catalogue! [buzz] Sears catalogue. [ding] Now, would you unhook this already?! I don't deserve this kind of shabby treatment! [buzz]
</quote>
<quote epno='7.01' title='Who Shot Mr. Burns? [Part Two]'>
Mr Burns: Officers, arrest the baby!
Chief Wiggum: Yeah, right, pops. No jury in the world is gonna convict a baby. Hmm... maybe Texas. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.02' title='Radioactive Man'>
Lisa: Cheer up, Bart. Milhouse is still going to need a true friend, someone to tell him he's great. Someone to rub lotion on him. Someone he can hurl whiskey bottles at when he's feeling low.
Bart: You're right, Lis! I can suck up to him! Like the religious people suck up to God!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.03' title='Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily'>
Child-Welfare Officer:  [looks at Maggie, who is wearing the "I'm a stupid baby" sign Bart originally put on Lisa] STUPID babies need the most attention! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.03' title='Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily'>
Homer: Okay, don't panic! To find Flanders, you just have to think like Flanders...
Homer's brain: I'm a big four-eyed lame-o and I wear the same stupid sweater everyday and-
Homer: The Springfield River! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.03' title='Home Sweet Homediddly-Dum-Doodily'>
Bart: Wow, Dad, you took a baptismal for me. How do you feel?
Homer: Oh, Bartholomew, I feel like St. Augustine of Hippo after his conversion by Ambrose of Milan.
Ned: Wait! Homer, what did you just say?
Homer: I said shut your ugly face, Flanders! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.04' title='Bart Sells His Soul'>
Bart: You shank! How could you squeal on me?!
Milhouse: Sorry Bart, but I don't want hungry birds pecking at my soul forever.
Bart: "Soul?" Come on Milhouse, there's no such thing as a soul. It's just something made up to scare kids, like the boogeyman or Michael Jackson!
Milhouse: But every religion says there's a soul, Bart. Why would they lie? What would they have to gain? [Cut to Rev. Lovejoy putting the money from the collection plate into a coin counter.]
Rev. Lovejoy: I don't hear scrubbing!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Homer: Are you saying you're never going to eat any animal again? What about bacon?
Lisa: No.
Homer: Ham?
Lisa: No!
Homer: Pork chops?
Lisa: Dad, those all come from the same animal!
Homer: Heh, heh, heh. Ooh, yeah, right, Lisa. A wonderful, magical animal. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Principal Skinner: Good morning, class. A certain...agitator...for privacy's sake let's call her "Lisa S." No, that's too obvious. Let's say "L. Simpson"...has raised questions about certain school policy. So in the interest of creating an open dialogue, sit silently and watch this film. [Skinner plays: The Meat Council Presents: Meat and You: Partners in Freedom. Number 3F03 in the 'Resistance is Useless' series.]
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Jimmy: I have this crazy friend who says it's wrong to eat meat. Is he crazy?
Troy McClure:[Laughing] No, Jimmy, just ignorant!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Troy Mclure: You see, your friend hasn't heard of the food chain. Just ask this scientitian.
Scientist: Uhhh...
Troy McClure: He'll tell you that one creature invariably eats another to survive. Don't kid yourself, Jimmy. If a cow got the chance he'd eat you and everyone you care about!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Jimmy: Wow, Mr. McClure, I was a Grade A Moron to ever question eating meat!
Troy McClure: Yes you were, Jimmy. Yes you were. [Playfully rubs Jimmy's head]
Jimmy: You're hurting me...
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Ralph: When I grow up I'm going to Bovine University!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.05' title='Lisa the Vegiterian'>
Apu: ...it's like Paul's song, "Live and Let Live".
Paul McCartney: Actually, it was "Live and Let Die".
Apu: Whatever, whatever. It had a good rhythm! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.06' title='Treehouse of Horror VI'>
Lisa: Do you understand what this means, Bart? The next time we fall asleep, we could die!
Grandpa: Eh, welcome to my world! [falls asleep] 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.06' title='Treehouse of Horror VI'>
Homer's Brain: [as he enters the 3rd dimension] Oh, glory of glories! Oh, heavenly testament to the eternal majesty of God's creation!
Homer: Holy macaroni! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.07' title='King-Size Homer'>
Mr. Burns: [Mister Burns is directing the plant employees at aerobics.] Raise your left hock, aerate! Raise your right hock, aerate! Come on people! I want to see more Teddy Roosevelts and less Franklin Roosevelts! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.07' title='King-Size Homer'>
Mr. Burns: Homer, your quick-thinking and bravery have turned a potential Chernobyl into a mere Three Mile Island. Bravo!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.07' title='King-Size Homer'>
Lisa: I still consider it ironic that Dad's girth saved the day, while a slimmer man would have falled to his death.
Bart: And I consider it ironic that, for once, Dad's butt actually prevented the release of toxic ga...
Marge: BART!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.07' title='King-Size Homer'>
Mr. Burns: Now Homer, if there is anything else I can do for you, please let me know. [Homer looks at his family, and realizes his obesity is making life hard for them.]
Homer: Can you please make me thin again?
Mr. Burns: I guarantee it! [Nighttime. Homer and Burns are now the only ones at plant. Burns is frustrated by Homer's girth and straining himself to do situps.]
Mr. Burns: One. One. ONE! [Burns throws down his megaphone in frustration]
Mr. Burns: Bah! I'll just pay for the blasted liposuction!
Homer: WOO-HOO!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.09' title='Sideshow Bobs Last Gleaming'>
Airman: And at this point in time, I would like to direct your attention to the particular air-vehicle next to which I am currently standing: the Harrier jet, one of our more dollar-intensive ordnance loadery vectors.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.09' title='Sideshow Bobs Last Gleaming'>
Airman: [Talking about a Harrier jet] Although it looks very complicated, I assure you, it is so well designed that even a child could fly it.
Lisa: Can I fly it?
Airman: Of course you cannot.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.09' title='Sideshow Bobs Last Gleaming'>
Bart: Look at that hunk of junk!
Grandpa: [sputters] You're ignorant! That's the Wright Brothers' plane! In Kitty Hawk in 1903, Charles Lindbergh flew it 15 miles on a thimble full of corn oil. Single-handedly won us the Civil War, it did!
Bart: How do you know so much about history, Grandpa?
Grandpa: I pieced it together, mostly from sugar packets!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.10' title='The Simpsons 138th Episode Spectacular'>
Bart: I'd sell my soul for a formula one racing car.
[Devil Flanders appears with a formula one racing car]
Devil Flanders: Heh, heh, heh, that can be arranged.
Bart: Changed my mind. Sorry.
[Devil Flanders vanishes]
Marge: Bart, stop pestering Satan!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.11' title='Marge Be Not Proud'>
Bart: [contemplates stealing a copy of "Bonestorm," he imagines several video game characters talking to him.]
Luigi: Go ahead, Bart. Take-a the "Bonestorm!"
Mario: The store, she's so rich! She'll-a never notice!
Donkey Kong: Duh, it's the company's fault for making you want it so much!
Lee Carvello: Don't do it, son. How's that game gonna help your putting?
Sonic the Hedgehog: Just take it! Takeit-takeit-takeit-takeit-takeit! TAKE IT!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.11' title='Marge Be Not Proud'>
Bart: I'd like to buy a copy of "Bonestorm." Here's 99 cents.
Comic Book Guy: [sighs] Allow me to summarize the proposed transaction. You wish to purchase "Bonestorm" for 99 cents. Net profit to me: negative 59 dollars. [opens the cash register] Please take my 59 dollars, I don't want it. [Bart reaches forward to take the cash.]Uh uh - Seeing as you are unfamiliar with sarcasm, I shall close the cash register at this point, and state that 99 cents is the rental price.
Bart Then may I please rent it, please???
Comic Book Guy No you may not, I am all out, though I do have a surprising abundance of "Lee Carvallo's Putting Challenge."
</quote>
<quote epno='7.12' title='Team Homer'>
Moe: You go through life, you try to resist the urge to punch people in the face, and for what? For some pimply little puke to treat you like dirt! Well, I'm better than dirt! Well... most kinds of dirt. I mean, not that fancy store-bought dirt. That stuff's loaded with nutrients. I... I can't compete with that stuff.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.12' title='Team Homer'>
Bart: Mom, my slingshot doesn't fit in these pockets. And these shorts leave nothing to the imagination. These uniforms suck!
Marge: Bart! Where do you pick up words like that?
Homer: [on phone] Yeah, Moe, that team sure did suck last night. They just plain sucked! I've seen teams suck before, but they were the suckiest bunch of sucks that ever sucked.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.12' title='Team Homer'>
Marge: Homerrr!
Homer: Aw, I gotta go. My damn wiener kids are listening. [hangs up]
Lisa: We are not wieners!
Homer: Then why are you dressed like that for?
Bart and Lisa: [in unison] They made us!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.13' title='Two Bad Neighbors'>
George Bush: If he thinks George Bush won't go into the sewer, well then he doesn't know George Bush.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.13' title='Two Bad Neighbors'>
Grandpa: Big deal! When I was a pup, we got spanked by Presidents till the cows came home. Grover Cleveland spanked me on two non-consecutive occasions!
Marge: Grandpa, we know in your day, spanking was common. But Homer and I don't believe in that kind of discipline!
Grandpa: And that's why your no-good kids are running wild! [He points over at Lisa, in a beanbag chair, reading. She looks up, confused.] 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.14' title='Scenes from the Class Struggle in Springfield'>
Homer: Look at these low, low prices on famous brand-name electronics!
Bart: Don't be a sap, Dad. These are just crappy knock-offs!
Homer: Pfft! I know a genuine Panaphonics when I see one! And look, there's Magnetbox and Sorny! 
</quote>

<quote epno='7.15' title='Bart the Fink'>
Cayman Islands Offshore Holding Corporation Manager: [chuckles] Oh, I'm sorry. But I can't divulge any information about that customer's secret, illegal account. [hangs up phone] ...Oh, crap. I shouldn't have said he was a customer... oh, crap. I shouldn't have said it was a secret... oh, crap! I certainly shouldn't have said it was illegal...! [sits back, fanning himself] Ah, it's too hot today.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.15' title='Bart the Fink'>
Krusty: But I can't go to jail! I got a swanky lifestyle! I'm used to the best!
IRS Agent #1: Krusty, this is America. We don't send our celebrities to jail. We'll just garnish your salary.
Krusty: Garnish my celery?
IRS Agent #2: Krusty please, no jokes.
Krusty: Who's joking? Oh, it all sounds crazy to me!
IRS Agent #1: It simply means we will be taking part of your salary until the debt is repaid. Let's say, 75% for the next 40 years.
Krusty: But I don't plan to live that long!
IRS Agent #2: Better make it 95%.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.16' title='Lisa the Iconoclast'>
Edna Krabappel: "Embiggens"? I never heard that word before I came to Springfield.
Miss Hoover: I don't know why. It's a perfectly cromulent word.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.16' title='Lisa the Iconoclast'>
Homer: [ringing bell] Hear ye, hear ye! Ye olde town crier proclaimed crappy by all! Chooseth Homer Simpson, and he shalt rock thy world!
Chief Wiggum: My God, he is fabulous!
Principal Skinner: He's embiggened that role with his cromulent performance. 
</quote>

<quote epno='7.17' title='Homer the Smithers'>
Homer: Here are your messages: "You have 30 minutes to move your car," "You have 10 minutes," "Your car has been impounded," "Your car has been crushed into a cube," "You have 30 minutes to move your cube."
[phone rings]
Homer: [answering] Yello, Mr. Burns's office.
Burns: Is it about my cube? 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.17' title='Homer the Smithers'>
Smithers: So, Mister Burns can now do all his work for himself, but I will wager you dollars to donuts he can't handle a call from his mother!
Homer: Mister Burns' mother is still alive?
Smithers: They haven't spoken in 50 years. He never forgave her for that affair with President Taft!
Homer: [chuckling] Taft, you old dog! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.18' title='The Day the Violence Died'>
Chester: He didn't create Itchy: I did.
Bart: Huh?
Chester: He stole the character from me in 1928. When I complained, his thugs kicked me out of his office, and dropped an anvil on me. Luckily, I was carrying an umbrella at the time. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.18' title='The Day the Violence Died'>
Bart: What the hell is this?
Lisa: It's one of those campy '70s throwbacks that appeals to Generation X'ers.
Bart: We need another Vietnam to thin out their ranks a little!
</quote>
<quote epno='7.18' title='The Day the Violence Died'>
Anon: Ok, maybe my dad did steal Itchy. So what? Animation is built on plagiarism. If it weren’t for someone plagiarizing the Honeymooners we wouldn’t have the Flintstones. If someone hadn’t ripped off Sergeant Bilko, there’d be no Top Cat. Huckleberry Hound, Chief Wigam, Yogi Bear, hah! Andy Griffin, Edward G. Robberson, Art Carnie. Your honor, you take away our right to steal ideas, where are they gonna come from?
</quote>
<quote epno='7.19' title='A Fish Called Selma'>
Marge: What are you talking about?
Homer: You know, his bizarre personal life. Those weird things they say he does down at the aquarium. Why, I heard...
Marge: Oh, Homer, that's just an urban legend. People don't do that kind of thing with fish! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.19' title='A Fish Called Selma'>
Louie: Troy McClure!? You said he was dead!
Fat Tony: No, what I said is that he sleeps with the fishes! You see...
Louie: Uh, Tony, please, no. I just ate a whole plate of dingamagoo. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.20' title='Bart on the Road'>
Homer: Wanna bite of my doughnut?
Lisa: No, thanks. Do you have any fruit?
Homer: This has purple stuff inside. Purple is a fruit. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.20' title='Bart on the Road'>
Nelson: [in awe] What is this place?
Bart: Branson, Missouri. My dad says it's like Vegas... if it were run by Ned Flanders. 
</quote>

<quote epno='7.21' title='22 Short Films About Springfield'>
Sanjay: I wish you'd come to my party, Apu. You could use some merriment.
Apu Listen, serving the customer is merriment enough for me. [Bart pays for his gum] Thank you, come again. You see? Most enjoyable.
Sanjay: Oh, I guarantee a wingding of titanic proportions. You will be there or kindly be square.
Apu: Well, I don't like to leave the store... [dusts off a "back in 5 minutes" sign] ...but for the next five minutes I'm going to party like it's on sale for 19.99! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.21' title='22 Short Films About Springfield'>
Chairman: Dr. Nick, this malpractice committee has received a few complaints against you. [reads from clipboard] Of the 160 gravest charges, the most troubling are performing major operations with a knife and fork from a seafood restaurant...
Dr Nick: But I cleaned them with my napkin.
Chairman: Misuse of the cadavers.
Dr Nick: I get here earlier when I drive in the carpool lane. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.22' title="Raging Abe Simpson and His Grumbling Grandson in 'The Curse of the Flying Hellfish'">
Bart: Sorry I made you lose the treasure, Grandpa.
Grandpa: The treasure's not important, boy; the most important thing is that you're safe. Now, let's go get that treasure! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.22' title="Raging Abe Simpson and His Grumbling Grandson in 'The Curse of the Flying Hellfish'">
Bart: Grandpa, do you think I could have been in the Flying Hellfish?
Grandpa: You're a give-em'-hell daredevil with a never-say-die attitude and a fourth-grade education! You could have made sergeant! 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.23' title='Much Apu About Nothing'>
Marge: What you're saying is so understandable. And really, your only crime was violating U.S. law. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.23' title='Much Apu About Nothing'>
Homer: Please identify this object.
Apu: It appears to be the flag that disappeared from the public library last year.
Homer: Correct. Now, we all know the thirteen stripes are for good luck, but why does the American flag have precisely forty-seven stars?
Apu: Because this particular flag is [chuckling] ridiculously out of date! The library must have purchased it during the brief period in 1912 after New Mexico became a state but before Arizona did.
Homer: Uh... partial credit. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.24' title='Homerpalooza'>
Homer: Aww, it makes no sense; I haven't changed since high school and suddenly I'm uncool.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.24' title='Homerpalooza'>
Homer: [1974. Homer and Barney are singing off key to the tune of Leo Sayer's "Dancing"] You make me feel like dancin'!
Barney: [off-key] I wanna dance the night away!
Grampa Simpson: What the hell are you two doing?!
Homer: It's called "rocking out", dad. You're just not with it.
Grampa Simpson: I used to be with it, but then they changed what it was. Now what I'm with isn't it, and what's it seems weird and scary to me... and the same thing is going to happen to you!
Homer: No way, man! We're gonna keep on rockin' Forever! Forever! Forever! [fades to the current timeline]
Homer: [dejected] Forever... forever... 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.25' title='Summer of 4 Ft. 2'>
Marge: Well, did you call one of your friends?
Lisa: Hah! These are my only friends: grown up nerds like Gore Vidal, and even he's kissed more boys than I ever will.
Marge: Girls, Lisa. Boys kiss girls. 
</quote>
<quote epno='7.25' title='Summer of 4 Ft. 2'>
Homer: Yeah, um, give me one of those porno magazines, a large box of condoms, a bottle of Old Harper, a box of panty shields... [rapid undertone] and some illegal fireworks... [normal voice] and one of those disposable enemas. You know what, make it two.
Owner: My apologies sir, but the sale of fireworks is strictly prohibited in this state and is punishable by- [the only other customer in the store walks out the door] follow me.
</quote>
<quote epno='7.25' title='Summer of 4 Ft. 2'>
Erin: So, you like hanging out?
Lisa: Well, it beats doin' stuff.
Erin: Totally. Stuff sucks. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.01' title='Treehouse of Horror VII'>
Marge: [has given birth to identical Siamese Twins. One of them starts gnawing on the other's arm.] I think I'll bottle-feed that one...
</quote>
<quote epno='8.01' title='Treehouse of Horror VII'>
Doctor Hibbert: But what to do about poor Hugo? Too crazy for Boys' Town, too much of a boy for Crazy Town. Until Mr. and Mrs. Simpson came up with the only humane action possible...
Homer: We chained Hugo up in the attic like an untrained animal and fed him a bucket of fish heads once a week.
Marge: It saved our marriage!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.01' title='Treehouse of Horror VII'>
George Stephanopoulos: [to Kodos] Uh, Mr. President, Sir. People are becoming a bit... confused by the way your and your opponent are, well, constantly holding hands.
Kodos: We are merely exchanging long protein strings. If you can think of a simpler way, I'd like to hear it! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.01' title='Treehouse of Horror VII'>
Fake Bill Clinton: My fellow Americans. As a young boy, I dreamed of being a baseball, but tonight I say, we must move forward, not backward, upward not forward, and always twirling, twirling, twirling towards freedom. [crowd cheers]
</quote>
<quote epno='8.02' title='You Only Move Twice'>
Scorpio: Good afternoon, gentlemen. This is Scorpio. I have the Doomsday Device. You have 72 hours to deliver the gold or you'll face the consequences. And to prove I'm not bluffing, watch this. [presses a button causing a bridge to blow up in the background of the screen the gentlemen are visible in]
UN Man 1: [all the men look at the explosion] Oh My God, the Fifty-Ninth Street Bridge!
UN Man 2: Maybe it just collapsed on its own.
UN Man 1: We can't take that chance.
UN Man 2: You always say that. I want to take a chance!
Scorpio: [scoffs] Collapsed on its own--you sh...You have seventy-two hours. See ya. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.02' title='You Only Move Twice'>
Scorpio: [Homer has just walked in on Scorpio, who is tuning a giant death ray.] By the way, Homer, what's your least favorite country, Italy or France?
Homer: France.
Scorpio: [laughs] Nobody ever says Italy. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.03' title='The Homer They Fall'>
Barney: You'd never get me in a ring - boxing causes brain damage. [drinks from a can of varnish] 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.03' title='The Homer They Fall'>
Kent Brockman: [after being booed by the crowd at the fight]: This just in: go to Hell! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.04' title='Burns, Baby Burns'>
Mr. Burns: I should've known you were the only one stupid enough to kidnap you! Now get down here so I can spank you in front of this gawking rabble. Smithers, take off my belt.
Smithers: With pleasure, sir! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.05' title='Bart After Dark'>
Marge: Now the cat needs his medication--
Homer: No problem.
Marge: --every morning and the furnace--
Homer: Can do.
Marge: --has been putting off--
Homer: Right.
Marge: --a lot of carbon monoxide--
Homer: Uh-huh.
Marge: --so keep the window open.
Homer: Gotcha - cat in the furnace!
Marge: Hmm, you know, I think I'll take Maggie with us. And if anything happens, just use your best judgm... mmm... just do what I would do. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.05' title='Bart After Dark'>
Belle: [through intercom]: Who is it?
Ned: Er, it's an angry mob, ma'am. Could you step outside for a twinkle while we knock down your house?
Belle: Just a minute. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.06' title='A Milhouse Divided'>
Kirk: You're letting me go!?
Cracker Co. Foreman: Kirk. Crackers are a family food - happy families. Maybe single people eat crackers, we don't know. Frankly, we don't want to know. It's a market we can do without!
Kirk: So that's it? After twenty years, "So long, good luck?"
Cracker Co. Foreman: I don't recall saying, "Good luck." 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.06' title='A Milhouse Divided'>
Nelson: Hey, van Houten, I heard your folks broke up.
Milhouse: Aren't you gonna say, "Haw-haw!"?
Nelson: Oh, by no means. [sits down]: My dad left my mom when she got hooked on cough drops. By the end [voice breaks], her breath was so fresh...she wasn't really my mother anymore.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.06' title='A Milhouse Divided'>
Milhouse: Oh, so I'm not alone.
Kearney: Ah, you'll do fine. My divorce was tough on my kid [slides over and reveals a child who bears a strong resemblance to Kearney], but he got over it.
Kearney's Son: I sleep in a drawer.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.07' title="Lisa's Date with Density ">
Dolph: Oh, man! You kissed a girl!
Jimbo: That is so gay!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.07' title="Lisa's Date with Density ">
Marge: Well most women will tell you that you're a fool to think you can change a man, but those women are quitters!
Lisa: What?
Marge: When I first met your father, he was loud, crude, and piggish. But I worked hard on him, and now he's a whole new person.
Lisa: Mom...?
Marge: He's a whole new person, Lisa. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Ned: Why me, Lord? I've always been good. I don't drink or dance or swear. I've even kept kosher just to be on the safe side. I've done everything the Bible says! Even the stuff that contradicts the other stuff! What more can I do? I...I..I feel like I wanna yell out, but I just can't dang-darn-diddly-darn-dang-ding-dong-diddly-darned do it! I just...I...*sigh*.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Homer: [Ned's poorly built, new house collapses] Aw, shoot. [Ned sighes and cleans his glasses. The lens snap off, and Ned sighes again, and put them on]
Ned: Calm down, Nedilly-diddly-diddly-diddly-doodly, they did their best, shodilly-iddly-iddly-diddly. Gotta be nice, hostiddly-iddly-diddly-diddly... AW, HELL-DIDDLY-DING-DONG-CRAP! CAN'T YOU MORONS DO ANYTHING RIGHT?! [Everyone gasps]
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Marge: Ned, we meant well. And everyone here tried their best...
Ned: Well, my family and I can't live in good intentions, Marge! Oh, your family's out of control, but we can't blame you, because you have goooooooood intentions!
Bart: Hey, back off, man!
Ned: Ooh, OK, duuuuude! I wouldn't want you to have a cow, maaaaaaan! Here's a catchphrase you better learn for your adult years: "Hey, buddy, got a quarter?!" [Everyone gasps again]
Bart: I am shocked and appalled.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Lisa: Mr Flanders, with all due respect, Bart didn't do ANYTHING.
Ned: [gasps sarcastically] Do I hear the sound of butting in? That's gotta be little Lisa Simpson, Springfield's answer to A QUESTION NO ONE ASKED!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Ned: What do we have here? [He shakes Chief Wiggum's belly] The long, flabby arm of the law? The last case you got to the bottom of was a case of MALLOMARS!
Krusty: [Writing in a notebook] Mallomars, oh, that's going in the act.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Ned: Oh, yeah, the clown. The only one of you buffoons who DOESN'T make me laugh. [To Lenny] And as for you, I don't know you but I'm sure you're a jerk!
Lenny: Hey, I've only been here a few minutes, what's going on?
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Ned: [To Moe] You ugly, hate-filled man!
Moe: Hey, hey, I may be ugly and hate-filled, but I... Um, what was the third thing you said?
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Ned: [calmly] Homer... you are the worst human being I have EVER met.
Homer: Hey, I got off pretty easy.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.08' title='Hurricane Neddy'>
Bart: [The Simpsons are trying to solve a Rubik's cube as a family] Turn the middle side topwise. Topwise! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.09' title='El Viaje Misterioso de Nuestro Jomer'>
Bart: [sees Homer's figure in the lighthouse light] Hey Lis! Is that dad?
Lisa: Either that, or Batman's really let himself go. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.09' title='El Viaje Misterioso de Nuestro Jomer'>
Homer: I always just figured my wife was my soulmate. But if it's not Marge, then who is it? Where do I begin looking?
Man: This really goes beyond my training as a furniture salesman, sir. Now if you don't want the sofa, I'll have to ask you to leave.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.09' title='El Viaje Misterioso de Nuestro Jomer'>
Homer: ... and that talking coyote was just a talking dog.
dog: Find your soulmate, Homer.
Homer: Wait a minute! Dogs don't talk!
dog: Woof! Woof!
Homer: Damn straight! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.10' title='The Springfield Files'>
Leonard Nimoy: Hello. I'm Leonard Nimoy. The following tale of alien encounters is true. And by true, I mean false. It's all lies. But they're entertaining lies. And in the end, isn't that the real truth? The answer is: No.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.10' title='The Springfield Files'>
Homer: This Friday, we're going back to the woods and we're going to find that alien!
Bart: What if we don't?
Homer: We'll fake it, and sell it to the Fox network.
Bart: [chuckles] They'll buy anything.
Homer: Now son, they do a lot of quality programming, too. [They both burst into laughter]
Homer: I kill me. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.11' title='The Twisted World of Marge Simpson '>
Marge: What's my territory?
Frank Ormand: Your territory? Well, let me put it this way: wherever a young mother is ignorant as to what to feed her baby, you'll be there. Wherever nacho penetration is less than total, you'll be there! Wherever a Bavarian is not quite full, you'll be there!
Marge: Don't forget fat people! They can't stop eating!
Homer: [passing by] Hey! Pretzels!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.11' title='The Twisted World of Marge Simpson '>
Marge: Are you sure the children will get enough nutrition from these pretzels?
Skinner: [monotonous] Yes I am sure. [a bandaged hand gives Marge money] Sure as sure can be.
Marge: Oh my God. What happened to your fingers?
Legs: [off-camera] Boating accident.
Skinner: I believe it was a... boking accident. [a laser sight is aimed at his temple] I have to go now.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.11' title='The Twisted World of Marge Simpson '>
Marge: Homer, did you tell the mob they could eliminate my competition with savage beatings and attempted murders?!
Homer: In those words...? [thinks] ...yes 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.12' title='Mountain of Madness'>
Homer: So, Burns is gonna make us all go on a stupid corporate retreat up in the mountains to learn about teamwork. Which means we'll have to cancel our plans to hang around here.
Bart: Teamwork is overrated.
Homer: Huh?
Bart: Think about it. I mean, what team was Babe Ruth on? Who knows.
Lisa and Marge: Yankees.
Bart: Sharing is a bunch of bull, too. And helping others. And what's all this crap I've been hearing about tolerance?
Homer: Hmm. Your ideas are intriguing to me and I wish to subscribe to your newsletter.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.12' title='Mountain of Madness'>
Burns: Ah sitting, the great leveler. From the lowliest peasant to the mightest pharoah, who does not enjoy a good sit?
</quote>
<quote epno='8.12' title='Mountain of Madness'>
Homer: Here is a little move I have been working on. Suppose you wanted that bowl of dip at the other end of the table.
Mr. Burns: Why Homer, you would have to get up.
Homer: Would I? Watch this.
Homer pounds table, which causes bowl to leap several times until it comes into Homer's hand
Mr. Burns: I am in your debt.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.13' title='Simpsoncalifragilisticexpiala[Annoyed Grunt]cious'>
Homer: All right, Marge, I'll get you your nanny. And to pay for it, I'll give up the Civil War re-creation society I love so much. [at Moe's, everyone, including Moe, is dressed like 1800s military generals]
Moe: [hangs up the phone] Well, Homer's out. We gotta find a new General Ambrose Burnside.
Barney: [dressed like Lincoln] And I'm not too crazy about our Stonewall Jackson.
Apu: [Apu emerges from the men's room dressed like a Hindu military official] The south shall come again! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.13' title="Simpsoncalifragilisticexpiala[Annoyed Grunt]cious">
Kearney: [As they walk through the park, things look more and more like nineteenth-century London] Extra, extra! Ripper strikes in Whitechapel!
Skinner: Boy for sale! Boy for sale!
Jimbo: Is this legal, man?
Skinner: Only here, and in Mississippi. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.14' title='The Itchy and Scratchy and Poochie Show'>
Doug: Uh question for Ms. Bellamy. In episode 2F09, when Itchy plays Scratchy's skeleton like a xylophone, he strikes the same rib twice in succession, yet he produces two clearly different tones. I mean, what are we to believe, that this is some sort of a... [the nerds chuckle] a magic xylophone or something? Boy, I really hope somebody got fired for that blunder.
June: Uh, well, uh...
Homer: I'll field this one. Let me ask you a question. Why would a man whose shirt says "Genius at Work" spend all of his time watching a children's cartoon show?
Doug: [embarrassed pause] I withdraw my question. [starts eating a candy bar]. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.14' title='The Itchy and Scratchy and Poochie Show'>
Bart: It's back to the basics, classic Itchy and Scratchy.
Lisa: We should thank our lucky stars that they're still putting on a program of this caliber after so many years.
Bart: What else is on? [Lisa changes the channel.] 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
Homer: [Bart walks in wearing a flamboyand Hawaiian shirt.] Hey, boy, where’d you get that shirt?
Bart: I dunno. Came outta the closet. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
i    Homer: Marge, the boy was wearing a Hawaiian shirt!
Marge: So?
Homer: There’s only two kind of guys who wear those shirts: gay guys and big, fat party animals, and Bart doesn’t look like a big, fat party animal to me!
Marge: So, if you wore a Hawaiian shirt, it wouldn’t be gay?
Homer: Right! Thank you. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
Homer: ...And the entire steel mill was gay.
Moe: Pfft, where you been, Homer? Entire steel industry's gay! Yeah, aerospace too. And the railroads! And you know what else? Broadway!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">

Homer: I like my beer cold, my T.V loud and my homosexuals fa-laming!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
Steel Mill Worker #3: Hot stuff coming through.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
Bart: Something about a bunch of guys alone together in the woods...seems kinda gay.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.15' title="Homer's Phobia">
Moe: Come on, don't take this so hard, Homer. You still got that other kid, uh... Lisa. Let's, uh, take her out hunting tomorrow; make her into a man.
Homer: Aw, she'd never go. She's a vegetarian.
Moe: Oh, geez! Homer, geez! You and Marge ain't cousins, are you? 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.16' title='Brother from Another Series'>
Bart: [seeing Krusty perform at prison] Wow! Those cons love Krusty! I guess inside every hardened criminal beats the heart of a ten-year-old boy
Lisa: And vice versa. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.16' title='Brother from Another Series'>
Sideshow Bob: You wanted to be Krusty's sidekick since you were five! What about the buffoon lessons, the four years at clown college.
Cecil: I'll thank you not to refer to Princeton that way. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.17' title='My Sister, My Sitter'>
Chief Wiggum: Bye, Lisa! If anything goes wrong, just dial 911! Uh, unless it's an emergency!
Lisa: G'bye, Chief! Enjoy Bob Saget!
Chief Wiggum: Heh, it's Bob Seger! [He looks at the tickets and frowns] Aw, crap! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.17' title='My Sister, My Sitter'>
Ned: Homer, I've got a Fozzie of a bear of a problem! See, Maude and her mother were visiting Tyre and Sidon, the twin cities of the Holy Land. Well, they must have kneeled in the wrong place and prayed to the wrong god because they're being held prisoner by militants of some sort!
Homer: Militants, eh? Well if I were you, I'd kick their asses.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.17' title='My Sister, My Sitter'>
Ned: Well anywhodilly-doodle, the police say it's just a routine hostage-taking, but I gotta drive to Capitol City and fill out some forms to get them out. Could you possibly watch the kids tonight?
Homer: Oh, gee, I'd really love to wanna help you, Flanders but...Marge was...taken prisoner in the....Holy Land, and...
</quote>
<quote epno='8.17' title='My Sister, My Sitter'>
Lisa: [tugging at Homer's hand] I'll do it! I'll babysit!
Ned: I dunno, Lisa. You're awfully young and the boys can be quite a handful. Todd's been pinching everyone lately!
Lisa: But I'm smart and responsible and my parents will be right next door!
Ned: Well, whaddya say, Homer? Can Lisa babysit my kids?
Lisa: Please, please, please!
Homer: Eh, I'll have to ask her. [He slams the door.]
</quote>
<quote epno='8.18' title='Homer vs. The Eighteenth Amendment'>
Mayor Quimby: You can't seriously want to ban alcohol! It tastes great, makes women appear more attractive and makes a person virtually invulnerable to criticism!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.18' title='Homer vs. The Eighteenth Amendment'>
Homer: To alcohol! The cause of, and solution to, all of lifes problems.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.19' title='Grade School Confidential'>
Skinner: [Bart has seen Principal Skinner and Mrs. Krabappel kissing.] Now, Bart...son...I don't know what you think you saw but let me assure you that...
Mrs. Krabappel: What Seymour..I mean, what Principal Skinner means, Bart, is that sometimes a little boy's imagination can run away with him!
Bart: That's the best you can do? You could have at least said you were giving her CPR or rehearsing a play!
Skinner: Is it...too late to say that?
Bart: Mmm-hmm! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.19' title='Grade School Confidential'>
Homer: Wait a minute! Bart's teacher's name is Krabappel? I've been calling her Krandall! Why didn't anybody tell me? I've been making an idiot out of myself!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.20' title='The Canine Mutiny'>
Marge: Aww, Maggie, you got oatmeal all over. Homie, would you clean her off?
Homer: Can do. [puts Maggie on the floor] Laddie! [whistling] Come here, boy! Who wants to lick a messy baby? 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.21' title='The Old Man and the Lisa'>
Mr. Burns: Oooh, so Mother Nature needs a favor?! Well maybe she should have thought of that when she was besetting us with droughts and floods and poison monkeys! Nature started the fight for survival, and now she wants to quit because she's losing. Well I say, hard cheese.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.22' title='In Marge We Trust'>
Homer:Oh, I'd love to go with you honey, but I got a lot of work to do around the bed.
Marge: Homer, the Lord only asks for an hour a week.
Homer: Well in that case he should've made the week an hour longer. 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.23' title="Homer's Enemy">
Grimes: [Alarms blare and red lights go on at Homer's work station] Simpson, you've got a 5-13! [Homer glances at his watch] No, a 5-13! In your procedures manual? A 5-13? [Homer stares at his watch again] Look at your control panel!
Homer: Oh, a five thir-teen. I'll handle it. [Homer goes into his office and pours water on his control panel, shorting out the console and alarms]
Homer: That got it. [Grimes stares flabbergasted through his window.] 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.23' title="Homer's Enemy">
Homer: Oh, I can’t believe it. I got an enemy. Me, the most beloved man in Springfield.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.23' title="Homer's Enemy">
Moe: Ah, it's a weird world, Homer. As hard as it is to believe, some people don't care for me, neither.
Homer: No, I won't accept that.
Moe: No, it's true. I got their names written down right here on what I call my, uh, "enemies list." [reaches under the bar for a sheet of paper]
Barney: [takes list and reads it] Jane Fonda, Daniel Schorr, Jack Anderson... Hey! This is Richard Nixon's enemies list. You just crossed out his name and put yours.
Moe: Okay, gimmie that, gimmie it back. [takes list and writes] Barney Gumble.
</quote>
<quote epno='8.23' title="Homer's Enemy">
Grimes: [Homer has entered a powerplant-designing contest for children and won first prize. Mr Burns gives him a blue ribbon. Everyone cheers] I can't stand it any longer! This whole plant is insane! INSANE, I tell you! It... DAH! AAH! [He goes nuts and runs out into the corridor]
Grimes: I can be lazy too! [He yanks off his tie, and shakes his butt at one of the employees]
Grimes: Look at me! Hi, I'm a worthless employee, just like Homer Simpson! Give me a promotion! [He pulls up his pants and waddles away, cross-eyed, like a penguin. He runs into an office and grabs two donuts from a donut box]
Grimes: Ooh, I eat like a slob but nobody minds! [He scoffs down nearly all the donuts in the box, as Homer and Mr Smithers watch. He then runs into the men's bathroom]
Grimes: [off-screen] I'm peeing on the seat! Give me a raise! [He comes out of the bathroom and waves his hands in Homer's face]
Grimes: Now, I'm returning to work without washing my hands! But, it doesn't matter, because I'm Homer Simpson! [He runs into Homer's office and spins around in Homer's chair, as Homer, Smithers, Mr Burns and Carl watch]
Grimes: I don't need to do my work, 'cause someone else will do it for me! [He puts his feet up, and smacks himself on the forehead] D'oh, d'oh, d'oh!
Homer: Hey, you OK, Grimey? [Grimes gets up]
Grimes: I'm better than OK. I'm Homer Simpson.
Homer: He, he. You wish.
Grimes: Oh, hi, Mr Burns! I'm the worst worker in the world! Time to go home to my mansion and eat my lobster! [He walks over to some really dangerous-looking wires on the wall, as Homer, Mr Burns, Smithers, a woman, and an employee watch]
Grimes: What's this? "Extremely High Voltage". Well, I don't need safety gloves, because I'm Homer Sim... [Everyone winces as Grimes grabs the wires and gets electrocuted, killing himself] 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.24' title='The Simpsons Spin-Off Showcase'>
Wiggum: If it isn't my old friends from Springfield, the Simpsons! What brings you folks to New Orleans?
Bart: Mardi Gras, man! When the Big Easy calls, you gotta accept the charges.
Lisa: Chief Wiggum, I can't wait to hear about all the exciting, sexy adventures you're sure to have against this colorful backdrop.
Wiggum: Well golly, I'd love to chat, but my son's been kidnapped. You haven't seen him, have you? Caucasian male, between the ages of six and ten, thinning hair.
Homer: [points to Ralph and Big Daddy] Over there.
Ralph: [points to Chief Wiggum] Look Big Daddy, it's regular daddy!
</quote>
<quote epno='8.24' title='The Simpsons Spin-Off Showcase'>
Ralph: [to Chief Wiggum] Daddy, when I grow up, I wanna be just like you!
Skinner[aka Skinny Boy]: Better start eating, kid! 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.25' title='The Secret War of Lisa Simpson'>
Bart: Military school!? You guys lied to me!
Homer: Well, I'm sorry if you heard "Disneyland," but I distinctly said, "military school!" 
</quote>
<quote epno='8.25' title='The Secret War of Lisa Simpson'>
Cadet: I can't believe they let a girl in!
Cadet #2: Don't worry; we'll drive her out of the academy! That's why God invented hazing! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.01' title='The City of New York vs. Homer Simpson '>
Moe: [as Homer, Barney, Lenny, Carl, and the 2 barflies [Larry the Wife Dodger and Sam the Ear Bender] walk in] Yeah, alright, listen up guys, the Springfield Police have told me that 91% of all traffic accidents are caused by you six guys.
[Moe's regulars exchange high-fives and cheer in triumph.]
</quote>
<quote epno='9.01' title='The City of New York vs. Homer Simpson '>
Moe: Yeah, I know, I know, but the bad news is we gotta start having Designated Drivers. [the regulars moan and groan] We'll choose the same way they pick the Pope... [sets a giant glass jar with pickled eggs floating in it on the table] Everybody reach in and draw a pickled egg; whoever gets the black egg stays sober tonight.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.01' title='The City of New York vs. Homer Simpson '>
Homer: New York is a hellhole. And you know how I feel about hellholes!
Lisa: Dad, you can't judge a place you've never been to.
Bart: Yeah, that's what people do in Russia. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.01' title='The City of New York vs. Homer Simpson '>
Homer: I'm gettin' out of this town alive if it kills me!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.02' title='The Principal and the Pauper'>
Lisa: A rose by any other name would smell as sweet.
Bart: Not if you called 'em stench blossoms.
Homer: Or crapweeds.
Marge: I'd sure hate to get a dozen crapweeds for Valentine's Day. I'd rather have candy.
Homer: Not if they were called scumdrops. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.02' title='The Principal and the Pauper'>
Skinner: The judge offered me a choice: jail, the army, or apologize to the judge and old lady. Of course, if I knew there was a war going on, I probably would have apologized.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.03' title="Lisa's Sax">
Homer: Now son, on your first day of school, I'd like to pass along the words of advice my father gave me. [thinking what Grandpa told him]
Young Grandpa: Homer, you're as dumb as a mule and twice as ugly. If a strange man offers you a ride, I say take it!
Homer: Lousy traumatic childhood. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.04' title='Treehouse of Horror VIII'>
Mayor Quimby: You are all hereby found guilty of the crime of witchcraft. I sentence you hags to be burned at the stake until you are deemed fit to re-enter society.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.04' title='Treehouse of Horror VIII'>
Maude Flanders:[Looks at witches] Oh, Neddie, look at them up there, plotting our doom. They could force us to do wanton acts of carnality.
Ned Flanders:[scoffs] Yeah, that'll be the day. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.04' title='Treehouse of Horror VIII'>
Homer:You're mutants?
Moe:Uh, we don't like the word 'mutants', Homer. We prefer 'freaks' or 'monsters'. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.05' title='The Cartridge Family'>
Gun Shop Owner: Whoa, careful there, Annie Oakley.
Homer: I don't have to be careful, I've got a gun. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.05' title='The Cartridge Family'>
Marge: I'm sorry Homer, no weapons.
Homer: A gun is not a weapon. It's a tool. Like a butcher knife, or a harpoon, or...uh, a...an alligator.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.05' title='The Cartridge Family'>
Moe: [At an NRA meeting] So last night I was closing up the bar, when some young punk comes in and tries to stick me up.
Sideshow Mel: Whatever did you do, Moe?
Moe: Well, it coulda been a real ugly situation but, luckily, I managed to shoot him in the spine.
[Audience cheers and applauds]
Moe: Yeah. I guess the next place he robs better have a ramp! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.05' title='The Cartridge Family'>
Krusty: Hey, yutz! Guns aren't toys! They're for home defense, hunting dangerous or delicious animals and keepin' the King of England out of your face!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Todd Flanders:We don't have to play football, do we Daddy?
Ned Flanders:Oh, you betcha! Team sports will keep you away from temptations like rock music and girls.
Rod and Todd Flanders:Yaaaaay! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Marge:You shouldn't pressure Bart like that.
Homer:Well, if you have a better way of living through my son I'd like to hear it. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Homer:My father never believed in me. Well, I'm not gonna make the same mistake. From now on I'm gonna be kinder to my son, and meaner to my dad.[Homer walks outside to where he forced Bart to run laps] Quit runnin' son. I just wanna give you a big hug.
Bart's mind: It's gotta be a trick, run like the wind. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Homer:[talking to his football team] Good practice team. Ok, its time for the easiest part of any coach's job-the cut. Now, while I wasn't able to cut everybody I wanted to, I have cut a lot of you. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Homer: Hello, son. I wanna apologize. I just got so caught up trying to encourage you I was blinded to your stinky performance. If you forgive me I promise I'll never encourage you again.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.06' title='Bart Star'>
Nelson's Father: Good game, son. Come on, I'm taking you to Hooters.
Nelson: Ah... I don't wanna bother mom at work. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.07' title='The Two Mrs. Nahasapeemapetilons'>
Apu: Is it just me or do all of your plans involve some horrible web of lies?
Homer: It's you. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.07' title='The Two Mrs. Nahasapeemapetilons'>
Grampa:Baloney! You came here to put me in a home.
Homer: You're already in a home.
Grampa: Oh how could you! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.07' title='The Two Mrs. Nahasapeemapetilons'>
Homer:Moe, what do you recommend for severe depression?
Moe:Booze, booze, and more booze.
Lenny:Ha. Nothing like a depressant to chase the blues away. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Lisa: Principal Skinner. Remember when I didn't sue when I found that scorpion in my applesauce? Well I'm calling in a favor.
Principal Skinner: I knew this day would come. [voice over intercom]: Attention all honor students will be rewarded with a trip to an archeological dig. Conversely, all detention students will be punished with a trip to an archaeological dig. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Homer: [scoffs] Facts are meaningless. You can use facts to prove anything that's remotely true.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Marge: Lisa, if you can't make a leap of faith now and then, well I feel sorry for you. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Moe: Science! What has science ever done for us?
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Flanders: Well, I gotta say, Lisa, it sounds like you're strainin' to do some explainin'.
Chief Wiggum: Yeah, everyone's heard of angels, but who's ever heard of a "Neanderthal"?
Lisa: It could be anything! It could be a mutant from the nuclear plant!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Mr. Burns: Oh, fiddle faddle, everyone knows our mutants have flippers. Oops, I've said too much. Smithers, use the amnesia ray.
Smithers: You mean the revolver, sir?
Mr. Burns: Precisely. Be sure to wipe your own memory clear when you're finished.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.08' title='Lisa the Skeptic'>
Judge: Lisa Simpson, you are charged with destruction of an historic curiosity--a misdemeanor. But in a larger sense, this trial will settle the age-old question of science versus religion. Let the opening statements commence.
Prosecuting lawyer: Your Honor, over the coming weeks, and months, we intend to prove Lisa Simpson willfully destroyed--
Lenny: [points to window] There's the angel!
[Murmuring]
[The courtroom empties]
Judge: I find the defendant not guilty. As for Science versus Religion, I'm issuing a restraining order. Religion must stay 500 yards from Science at all times. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.09' title='Reality Bites'>
Homer:Trying is the 1st step toward failure.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.09' title='Reality Bites'>
Homer:Seat belts!? They kill more people than they save.
Lisa:That's not true. You're thinking of airbags! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.09' title='Reality Bites'>
Chief Wiggam:This is Wiggam, reporting a 318-waking a police officer!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.09' title='Reality Bites'>
Lionel Hutz: Marge, I had a lot of calls about you. Customers love your no-pressure approach.
Marge: Well, like we say, the right house for the right person.
Lionel Hutz: Listen, it's time I let you in on a little secret, Marge. "The right house" is the house that's for sale; the "right person" is anyone.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.09' title='Reality Bites'>
Marge: But all I did was tell the truth!
Lionel Hutz: Of course you did. But there's "the truth" [shakes head] and "the truth!" [smiles wide]. Let me show you.
Marge: It's awfully small.
Lionel Hutz: I'd say it's awfully "cozy."
Marge: That's dilapidated.
Lionel Hutz: Rustic.
Marge: That house is on fire!
Lionel Hutz: "Motivated seller"!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.10' title='Miracle on Evergreen Terrace'>
Sideshow Mel:You only live once!
Apu:Hey, speak for yourself! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.10' title='Miracle on Evergreen Terrace'>
Moe: [disillusioned] So this was all a scam. And on Christmas.
Barney: Yeah. Jesus must be spinning in his grave! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.10' title='Miracle on Evergreen Terrace'>
Homer:Marge, kids, let's go buy some happiness!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.12' title='Bart Carny'>
Nelson: You wrecked Hitler's car! What did he ever do to you? 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Homer:I always say-a boy can learn more at an airport then he can at any school.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Marge: I've never heard of these Movementarians; are they some kind of church?
Homer: Who cares what it is? The point is that these are some decent generous people that I can take advantage of.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Marge: But what if they try to talk us into something?
Homer: Marge, Marge, Marge [chuckles]. Remember when those smooth-talking guys tried to sell me a time-share vacation condo?
Marge: You bought four of them! Thank God the check bounced.
Homer: So I beat the system.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Lisa: Watch yourself, Dad. You're the highly suggestible type.
Homer: Yes, I am the highly suggestible type.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Rev. Lovejoy: [preaching at church] This so called "New Religion" is nothing more than a bunch of weird rituals designed to take away the money of fools. Now, let's say the Lord's Prayer 40 times but first let's pass the collection plate!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.13' title='The Joy of Sect'>
Lisa: It's wonderful to think for ourselves again.
Bart: You said it, sister.
TV voice-over: You are watching Fox.
Homer, Marge, Bart, and Lisa: We are watching Fox. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.14' title='Das Bus'>
Lisa: Point of order, if we want to learn anything, we must respect--
Bart: Point of "odor," Lisa stinks. [children laugh]
</quote>
<quote epno='9.14' title='Das Bus'>
Principal Skinner: [Principal Skinner restores order by banging his shoe on the desk] Order, order! Do you kids want to be like the real U.N., or do you just want to squabble and waste time?
</quote>
<quote epno='9.14' title='Das Bus'>
Bart: It'll be just like The Swiss Family Robinson, only with more cursing! We'll live like kings! Damn hell ass kings!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.14' title='Das Bus'>
Sherri/Terri: I'm so hungry I could eat at Arby's!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.14' title='Das Bus'>
Lisa: All we could find are these purple, oozing berries, and I don't think they're edible.
Ralph: I eated the purple berries.
Bart: How are they Ralph? Good?
Ralph: [collapsing in pain] They taste like burning. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.15' title='The Last Temptation of Krust'>
Krusty: Uh-huh. Charity, eh? What's my cut? Nothing? I make more than that takin' a "schwitz."
Jay Leno: He seems reluctant.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.15' title='The Last Temptation of Krust'>
Moe: Hi, how're you folks doin'? I'm Moe, or as the ladies like to call me,"hey you, behind the bushes". [the audience doesn't respond]; [Moe taps on the microphone] Is this thing on?
Barney: No. Sorry, Moe. [Turns on the microphone]
</quote>
<quote epno='9.16' title='Dumbbell Indemnity'>
Homer:[drunk at Moe's] Here's to Marge! And all the blissful years I've spent hiding from her in this bar!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.16' title='Dumbbell Indemnity'>
Homer:Don't give up Moe. The girl of your dreams has gotta be in some bar.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.16' title='Dumbbell Indemnity'>
Homer: Why don't you sell your car?
Moe: Ah, my car ain't worth nothing, but it is insured for five grand. Homer, you gotta steal the car for me and wreck it.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.16' title='Dumbbell Indemnity'>
Homer: Steal your car? I can just imagine what Marge would say.
Marge: [in thought balloon] Homer, I insist you steal that car!
Homer: I'll do it!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.16' title='Dumbbell Indemnity'>
Homer: Must kill Moe.... WHHHEEEEE!!!!! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.17' title='Lisa the Simpson'>
Grampa:[talking to Lisa] Your dad used to be as smart as a monkey. Then his mind started gettin' lazy. Now he's a dumb as a chimp.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.17' title='Lisa the Simpson'>
Troy McClure:Hi, I'm Troy McClure. You may remember me from such medical films as "Alice Doesn't Live Anymore" and "Mommy, What's Wrong with that Man's Face?"
</quote>
<quote epno='9.17' title='Lisa the Simpson'>
Grampa: [about Lisa] Aw, she's just upset 'cause I told her her brain's turnin' to mush. On accout of the Simpson Gene!
Marge: "Simpson Gene?" That's just foolishness!
Grampa: Nope. Baldness, too! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.18' title='This Little Wiggy'>
Ralph Wiggam:I found a moon rock in my nose.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.18' title='This Little Wiggy'>
Bart: Your dad is chief of police, doesn't he have any cool police stuff?
Ralph: Just in his closet, but he said I'm not allowed to go in there.
Bart: Did he say I'm not allowed to go in there?
Ralph: Yes. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.18' title='This Little Wiggy'>
Chief Wiggam:[to Ralph] You know you're not suppose to go in there. What is your fascination with my "Forbidden Closet of Mystery?"
</quote>
<quote epno='9.19' title="Simpson Tide">
Captain Tenille: I'm a man of few words. [long pause] Any questions?
Homer: Is a poop deck really what I think it is?
Captain Tenille: [chuckles] I like the cut of your jib.
Homer: What's a jib?
Captain Tenille: [laughs] Promote that man. 
</quote>

<quote epno='9.19' title="Simpson Tide">
Captain Tenille: Tell me young man, what do you want out of life?.
Homer: [straining to reach the peas on the table] I want peeeas...
Captain Tenille: Oh, we all want peace! But it's always just out of reach. [Homer groans and sits back in his chair] So, what's the best way to get peace?.
Homer: [reaching out and picking up peas on his knife] With a knife.
Captain Tenille: Exactly! Not with the olive branch but the bayonet! Ah, Simpson, you're like the son I never had.
Homer: And you're like the father I never visit. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.19' title="Simpson Tide">
Announcer: Daybreak: Jakarta. The proud men and women of the Navy are fighting for freedom. But you're in Lubbock, Texas, hosing stains off a monument. You're in the Naval Reserve. America's seventeenth line of defense, between the Mississippi National Guard, and the League of Women Voters. After basic training, you'll only have to work one weekend a month. And most of that time, you're drunk off your ass.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.20' title="The Trouble with Trillions">
Homer: [Scrambling to complete his taxes] Marge, how many kids do we have? Oh, no time to count, I'll just estimate! Uh . . . nine!
Marge:Homer, you know we don't have--
Homer: Shut up! Shut up! If I don't hear you, it's not illegal!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.20' title="The Trouble with Trillions">
Film Narrator: This film will self-destruct if it's not properly stored.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.20' title="The Trouble with Trillions">
Agent Johnson: We believe Burns still has that bill hidden somewhere in his house, but all we've ascertained from satellite photos is that it's not on the roof. That's where you come in! We need you to steal the trillion dollars from Mr. Burns.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.20' title="The Trouble with Trillions">
Mr. Burns:If it's a crime to love one's country, then I'm guilty. And if it's a crime to steal a trillion dollars from our government, and hand it over to communist Cuba, then I'm guilty of that too. And if it's a crime to bribe a jury, then so help me, I'll soon be guilty of that!
Homer:God bless America! 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.21' title="Girly Edition">
Store Clerk: May I inquire as to how you are differently abled?
Homer: Oh, I'm not handicapped. I'm just lazy. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.21' title="Girly Edition">
Mr. Burns: [sniffling] Smithers, do you think maybe my power plant killed those ducks?
Smithers: There's no maybe about it, sir.
Mr. Burns: Excellent.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.21' title="Girly Edition">
Lisa: They want sentiment? I'll pump 'em so full of sap they'll have to blow their nose with a pancake!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.22' title="Trash of the Titans">
Homer:I never apologize, Lisa. I'm sorry, but that's just the way I am.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.22' title="Trash of the Titans">
Homer: This is a very, very proud day for us! Especially me, your father, me, beat City Hall! It's just like David and Goliath, only this time, David won!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.22' title="Trash of the Titans">
Homer: [Homer unhinges briefcase to reveal stacks of money] Will cash do?
Head Garbageman: Will it ever! [Mayor Quimby barges into Homer's office]
Mayor Quimby: Did I just hear a briefcase opening?
</quote>
<quote epno='9.23' title="King of the Hill">
Rainier Wolfcastle: McBain to base! Under attack by Commie-Nazis!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.24' title="Lost Our Lisa">
Homer:I know I'm not normally a praying man, but if you're up there please save me Superman!
</quote>
<quote epno='9.24' title="Lost Our Lisa">
Homer:Stupid risks are what make life worth living.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.24' title="Lost Our Lisa">
Homer: Lisa, could you get the window? The police have Daddy's prints on file.
</quote>
<quote epno='9.24' title="Lost Our Lisa">
Lisa: [to herself] Huh, I didn't know Springfield had a Russian district. [comes across two men playing chess] Uh, excuse me. I'm kinda lost. Can you tell me how to get to the museum?
Man 1: [angrily] Moe udovoljstvie! Muzej - shestj blokov tot putj! [My pleasure! The museum is six blocks that way!] [Lisa runs off screaming]
Man 1: [calmly] Ona poshla nepraviljnыj putj. [She went the wrong way.]
Man 2: [makes his move] Porazhenie. [Checkmate.]
Man 1: [throws the board on the ground] Horoshaja igra! Kak o drugom?! [Good game! How about another?!]
</quote>
<quote epno='9.25' title="Natural Born Kissers">
Marge:You don't think there's anything wrong with what we're doing, do you?
Homer:I don't think anything I've ever done is wrong. 
</quote>
<quote epno='9.25' title="Natural Born Kissers">
Reverend: Now lets all thank the lord for this our new crystal church for us to behold all his natural glory.

[Homer's backside is sliding across the top of it the roof, making a huge noise]

Reverend: Now hurry, let's all look down and admire God's new parquet floor. [Eyes closed looking down as Homer still passes by on the ceiling] Eyes on the floor, still on the floor, always on God's floor. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Homer:Used grease is worth money? Then my arteries are clogged with yellow gold!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Homer:Marge, I'm a little busy right now achieving financial independence.
Marge:With cans of used grease?
Homer:[mockingly] No, through savings and wise investments! Of course with grease. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Alex: Your name's Lisa? Shut up, I love that name!
Lisa: Did she just tell me to "shut up?" 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Willie: not so fast, boyo. Hell, if it was up to me, I'd let ya go. [Raises his fists.] But, the lads have a temper, and they've been drinking all day! [Willie starts punching Homer with hard blows while Homer is screaming in pain.]
Homer: Ow! Stop pummeling me! It's really painful!
Willie: [Willie stops briefly.] Okay, fine. I'll strangle ya for a while! [Willie strangles Homer with his hose, and one of Homer's eyes bulges out of its socket.]
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Homer:Lisa, I can't imagine anyone being more likable than you. But apparently this new girl is. So my advice would be to start copying her in every way.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Homer:Oh, I can't believe those goons muscled me out of my grease business. I've been muscled out of everything I've ever done, including my muscle for hire business.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Marge:Oh, poor Homey. Couldn't you try some other far-out, moneymaking scheme?
</quote>
<quote epno='10.01' title="Lard of the Dance">
Homer:Alright son, we're about to embark on our most difficult mission. Let's bow our head in prayer. Dear Lord, I know you're busy, seeing as how you can watch women change cloths and all that, but if you help us steal this grease tonight I promise we'll donate half the profits to charity.
Bart:Dad, He's not stupid.
Homer:Alright, screw it. Let's go! [floors it] 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.02' title="The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace">
Marge:I brought you a tuna sandwich. They say it's brain food. I guess because there's so much dolphin in it, and you know how smart they are.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.02' title="The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace">
Kent Brockman:In other news, Thomas Edison-the greatest inventor of all time-is apparently still inventing despite the notable handicap of being dead.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.02' title="The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace">
Homer: [Homer is showing his family his new inventions.] This is my "Everything's Okay Alarm." [Picks up a device that looks like a smoke detector and presses a button. It starts beeping loudly.] [Homer shouting.] THIS ALARM WILL SOUND EVERY 3 SECONDS, UNLESS SOMETHING ISN'T OKAY!
Marge: HOMER, TURN IT OFF!
Homer: IT CAN'T BE TURNED OFF! [The beeping starts weakening, then stops completely.] But, it does break easily. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.02' title="The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace">
Lisa: Dad, women won't like being shot in the face.
Homer: Women will like what I tell them to like. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.03' title="Bart the Mother">
Nelson:What can I get for 8,000 tickets?
Clerk:Uh, a BB gun or an Easy Bake Oven.
Nelson:Hmmm...Hot food is tempting, but I just can't say no to a weapon. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.03' title="Bart the Mother">
Marge: Bart! Did you kill that poor bird?
Bart: I didn't mean to, Mom. The gun pulled to the left.
Marge: You disobeyed me, snuck over here, and murdered a helpless animal?!
Bart: I know, I really screwed up. I deserve to be punished.
Marge [sighs dejectedly]: Oh, what's the point, Bart? I punish, and I punish, and I punish, but it never sinks in. So you know what? Do what you want. You wanna play with little hoodlums? Fine! Have fun killing things! [gets in her stationwagon and drives off] 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.03' title="Bart the Mother">
Troy McClure: Hi, I'm Troy McClure. You may remember me from such nature films as "Earwigs, ewwww" and "Man vs. Nature: The Road to Victory"
</quote>
<quote epno='10.03' title="Bart the Mother">
Homer:This is the most exciting thing I've seen since Halley's Comet collided with the moon.
Lisa:That didn't happen Dad.
Homer:Sure it didn't Lisa. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.03' title="Bart the Mother">
Mayor Quimby:[to Bart] For decimating our pigeon population and for making Springfield a less oppressive place to while away our worthless lives, I present you with this scented candle.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.04' title="Treehouse of Horror IX">
Marge: Homer, Kang is Maggie's father.
Homer: [gasps] You intergalactic hussy! How could you?! [starts crying] Was he better than me? 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.05' title="When You Dish Upon a Star">
Lisa:[speaking to Homer] You promised to take us to the lake.
Homer:I promise you kids lots of things. That's what make me such a good father.
Lisa:Actually, keeping promises would make you a good father.
Homer:No that would make me a great father. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.05' title="When You Dish Upon a Star">
Man:Sir you can't operate a boat under the influence of alcohol.
Homer:Oh, that sounds like a wager to me. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.05' title="When You Dish Upon a Star">
Homer:[while parasailing] Ooh, I'm soaring like a candy wrapper caught in an updraft!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.05' title="When You Dish Upon a Star">
Homer: When was the last time Barbra Streisand ever did the laundry for you? And when it's time to do the dishes, where's Ray Bolger?! I'll tell you where! RAY BOLGER IS LOOKING OUT FOR RAY BOLGER!!!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.07' title="Lisa Gets an 'A'">
Skinner: And, for the first time ever, our computer lab actually has a computer in it!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.07' title="Lisa Gets an 'A'">
Ralph: [Ralph is sitting at their newly installed computer, engrossed in an educational spelling program] Hi, Lisa! Hi, Principal Skinner! Hi, Super Nintendo Chalmers! [he types "cat," which prompts a "meow" sound from the computer] I'm learn-ding.
Lisa: Aw, way to go, Ralph.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.07' title="Lisa Gets an 'A'">
Lisa: [outside the boys bathroom] Hey, I can't go in there!
Bart: Relax, there's nothing here you didn't see when Dad boycotted pants. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.08' title="Homer Simpson in : 'Kidney Trouble'">
Homer: If I die in the operation, will ya do one thing for me.
Marge: Oooh, anything sweetheart.
Homer: [serious tone] Blow up the hospital. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.09' title="Mayored to the Mob">
Mayor Quimby:Oh God. Can't this town go one day without a riot?
</quote>
<quote epno='10.09' title="Mayored to the Mob">
Homer: Oh My God, I killed the Mayor! Alright, stay calm. I'll just use the body to stage an elaborate farce a la Weekend At Bernie's.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.09' title="Mayored to the Mob">
Marge: You're guarding the mayor, after Fat Tony swore revenge?
Homer: I have to, Marge. Besides, those mobsters don't scare me. Bart, will you start daddy's car?
Marge: Homer!
Homer: What? Nothing bad will happen.
Bart: Well, then you start it.
Homer: Fine, I'll take a cab.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.10' title="Viva Ned Flanders">
Casino worker:Someone dishonoring their marriage vows!? Not in Las Vegas.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.11' title="Wild Barts Can't be Broken">    
Homer: Stupid Isotopes. Hurry up and lose so we can get outta here!
Lisa: Why do you hate the Isotopes so much, Dad?
Homer: Because I loved them once and they broke my heart. Let that be a lesson to you, sweetie. Never love anything.
Lisa: Even you?
Homer: Especially me.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.11' title="Wild Barts Can't be Broken">    
Marge: That's right! Like my mother always said, you've got to stick it out, even if you picked the loser ... [sees Homer picking at his ear and looking at his finger afterward] ...to the bitter end.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.11' title="Wild Barts Can't be Broken">    
Bart: Tune in tomorrow, and every day, until the curfew is lifted, because we'll be revealing embarrassing secrets about Springfield's other adults.
Homer: Well, at least they've already done me.
Bart: And we have plenty more on Homer Simpson.
Homer: D'oh! 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.13' title="Homer to the Max">
Marge: But I fell in love with Homer Simpson. I don't wanna snuggle with Max Power.
Max [Homer]: Nobody snuggles with Max Power - You strap yourself in and feel the G's! [performs a hip gyration]
Marge: Oh, Lord...
</quote>
<quote epno='10.13' title="Homer to the Max">
Max [Homer]: Kids, there's three ways to do things! The right way, the wrong way, and the Max Power way!
Bart: Isn't that the wrong way?
Max: Yeah, but faster!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.13' title="Homer to the Max">
Max [Homer]: Awww, this is the worst party ever.
Marge: Remember that New Year's Eve party at Lenny's? He didn't even have a clock. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.14' title="I'm With Cupid">
Homer: ...and then the handsome prince realized he had to go to the bathroom really bad, but the evil ogre -- Barney -- had left the men's room in the most wicked condition! So the prince went out back to the enchanted alley --
Lisa: That's not a fairy tale; it's something that happened to you at Moe's!
Homer: Sssh. Anyway, the prince passed out for a hundred years, until he was awakened by the kiss of a noble raccoon! 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.14' title="I'm With Cupid">
Homer Everybody's marriages is falling apart except ours. You see the problem is communication.... too much communication.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.14' title="I'm With Cupid">
Homer: People! It's easy to blame ourselves, but it's even easier to blame Apu!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.15' title="Marge Simpson in: 'Screaming Yellow Honkers'">
Bart Simpson: I didn't think it was physically possible, but this both sucks and blows. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.15' title="Marge Simpson in: 'Screaming Yellow Honkers'">
Homer:I'm gonna die! Jesus, Allah, Buddha, I love you all!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.16' title="Make Room for Lisa">
Homer: Relax, Lisa! Meet your new roommate! [Hums The Odd Couple Theme]
Bart: I'm gonna make your life a living hell!
Homer: [Still hums The Odd Couple and shoves Lisa in] 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Homer: Don't you have school?
Bart: Don't you have work?
Homer: Ahh, Touché. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Homer: Look son, it's one of nature's wonders-a convoy!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Homer: Oh yeah, I need something that will keep me awake, alert and restless all night long.
Old Clerk: Well Congress is racing back to Washington to outlaw these. [Pulls out a bottle labeled Stimu-crank]
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Homer: Sold! [Takes pills and eats them all]
Old Clerk: You can't take that many pep pills at once!
Homer: Don't worry. I'll balance it out with a bottle of sleeping pills.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Homer: What's happening to me? There's still food, but i don't wanna eat it. I've become everything I've ever hated! [cries]
</quote>
<quote epno='10.17' title="Maximum Homerdrive">
Bart: Dad, they're going to kill us!
Homer: Oh, why do all my trips end like this? 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.18' title="Simpsons Bible Stories">
Homer [as Adam]: [to Marge [as Eve]] You're pretty uptight for a naked chick.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.18' title="Simpsons Bible Stories">
Marge: Oh, no! It's the Apocalypse! Bart, are you wearing clean underwear?
Bart: Not anymore.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.18' title="Simpsons Bible Stories">
Lisa: It's The Rapture, and I never knew true love!
Homer: I never used those pizza coupons.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.18' title="Simpsons Bible Stories">
Milhouse as Moses: [Israelites reach the Red Sea as the Egyptians chase them] Screw this! I'm converting. Save us o mighty Ra!
</quote>
<quote epno='10.19' title="Mom and Pop Art">
Homer: [waking up] Oh, Marge! Why does art hate me? I never did anything to art. [He holds up his arm, his fist is through one of Andy Warhol's Soup Can paintings] Oh. Let's get out of here.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.19' title="Mom and Pop Art">
Homer [as he looks at a picture of "Life in Hell"'s Akbar and Jeff]: Matt Groening?! What's he doing in a museum? He can barely draw.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.20' title="The Old Mand and the 'C' Student">
Bart: Hey, Chalmers, where are you from?
Superintendent Chalmers: Well, I was born in Queens, went to Ball state, then made the move to Intercourse, Pennsylvania. Uh, why do you ask?
[Bart is about to say something when Skinner Quickly puts his hand over his mouth]
</quote>
<quote epno='10.20' title="The Old Mand and the 'C' Student">
Superintendent Chalmers: Now if you'll excuse me, I'm off to my vacation at Lake Titicaca. Try to make a joke out of that, Mr. Smart Guy.
[Bart looks at Skinner, and Skinner waves his hands "no"]
</quote>
<quote epno='10.21' title="Monty Can't Buy Me Love">
Mr Burns: It's time to win the love of these hate-filled morons.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.21' title="Monty Can't Buy Me Love">
Mr Burns: Simpson! I want to be loved.
Homer: Well, I'll need some beer. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.21' title="Monty Can't Buy Me Love">
Selma: Single? He passes the Selma test! 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.22' title="They Saved  Lisa's Brain">
Homer: You're not going to ask me to pose nude, are you?
Photographer: Well, yes, unless you have issues about revealing your body.
Homer: I don't, but the block association seems to. They wanted a "traditional" Santa.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.22' title="They Saved  Lisa's Brain">
Lisa: [writing her letter] We can better ourselves!
[Lisa then sees a naked Bart riding a pig in the hallway]
Lisa: [to herself] Well, most of us. 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.23' title="Thirty Minutes Over Tokyo">
PA: Welcome to Japan, folks. The local time is tomorrow.
</quote>
<quote epno='10.23' title="Thirty Minutes Over Tokyo">
Japanese toilet: Welcome. I am honored to accept your waste.
Homer: [gasps] They're years ahead of us! 
</quote>
<quote epno='10.23' title="Thirty Minutes Over Tokyo">
Homer: The internet? That thing is still around?
</quote>
<quote epno='11.01' title="Beyond Blunderdome">
Mel Gibson: John Travolta flew me in his jet. Now I have to help him move next weekend. He deliberately waited 'til we were in the air to ask me!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.01' title="Beyond Blunderdome">
Hannah: Oh, no! We killed Mel Gibson!
Christian: You all saw it. He came at me with a knife, right? 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.02' title="Brother's Little Helper">
Mark McGwire:Young Bart here is right. We are spying on you, pretty much around the clock.
Bart: But why, Mr. McGwire?
Mark McGwire: Do you want to know the terrifying truth, or do you want to see me sock a few dingers?
Crowd: Dingers! Dingers! 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.02' title="Brother's Little Helper">
Burns: Smithers, we're at war!
Smithers: I'll begin profiteering, sir.
Burns: And hoarding! Leave it to the Democrats to let the Spaniards back in the pantry!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.03' title="Guess Who's Coming to Criticize Dinner? ">
Homer: I smell cake! Cake that says [sniff sniff] "Farewell" and [sniff sniff] "Best Wishes"!
Nelson: Your old man has an awesome nose.
Bart: Oh, that's nothing. He can hear pudding. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.03' title="Guess Who's Coming to Criticize Dinner? ">
Newspaper editor: ...And to protect Mother Earth, each copy contains a certain percentage of recycled paper.
Lisa: And what percent is that?
Newspaper editor: Zero.
[Lisa frowns]
Newspaper editor: Zero’s a percent! 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.03' title="Guess Who's Coming to Criticize Dinner? ">
Marge: Only your father can take up a part-time job in a small town newspaper and end up the target of international assassins.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.04' title="Treehouse of Horror X">
Tom Arnold: My shows weren't great, but I never tied people up and forced them to watch. And I could've, because I'm a big guy and I'm good with knots.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.04' title="Treehouse of Horror X">
Homer: The sun?! That's the hottest place on Earth!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.05' title="E-I-E-I-[Annoyed Grunt]">
Bart: [after it's been decided that the family will live on Grampa's old farm] I'll dig an outhouse!
Lisa: I'll weed the floor!
Marge: I'll repress the rage I'm feeling! [plasters a fake smile on her face] 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.06' title="Hello Gutter, Hello Fadder">
Homer [in baby talk]: Look, Maggie, I'm Homie-Womie, the Teletubby. [sternly]: And I'm all man in case you heard otherwise!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.06' title="Hello Gutter, Hello Fadder">
Homer: [playing peek-a-boo] Where's Maggie? Where's Maggie? [uncovers his eyes] Hey, where is she?
</quote>
<quote epno='11.07' title="Eight Misbehavin'">
Apu: Here goes nothing.
Apu and Manjula: [as symbols appear on the pregnancy test] Baby... baby... lemon.
Manjula: All that sex for nothing.
Apu: Well, that is a pretty grim assessment.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.07' title="Eight Misbehavin'">
Manjula: [Apu is asleep with the babies] Apu, it's 4 am. You're late for work.
Apu: Oh. I just had the most beautiful dream where I died.
Manjula: Oh no you don't! Not til they're out of college.
Apu: Listen, I'll die when I want to!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.08' title="Take My Wife, Sleaze">
Homer: The first meeting of Hell's Satans comes to order.
Flanders: I move that we reconsider our club name. Make it something a little less blasphemous. After all we don't want to go to hell.
Lenny: How about the Devil's Pals.
Flanders: No, see-
Moe: Or the Christ Punchers! 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.09' title="Grift of the Magi">
Fat Tony: I don't get mad, I get stabby. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.10' title="Little Big Mom">
Lisa: [Lisa sends Bart off to school and Homer off to work.] Here are your lunches. And no trading them for fireworks!
Homer: Aww, but Lenny just got some bottle rockets!
Lisa: You stay away from Lenny! 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.11' title="Faith Off">
Homer: [Cooking meat] Okay, who needs another lamb rack? [Marge and Bart nod no] Lisa? Ham hock, Try tip?
Lisa: Do we have any food that wasn't brutally slaughtered?
Homer: Well I think the veal died of loneliness. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.11' title="Faith Off">
Bart: Hey Brother Faith, how did you get the bucket off my dad's head?
Brother Faith: Well I didn't son, you did. God has given you the power.
Bart: Really? Hmmm.. I would think he would want to limit my power. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.12' title="The Mansion Family">
Mr Burns: Let's see, social security number: naught, naught, naught ... naught, naught ... naught, naught, naught, two. Damn Roosevelt! Cause of parents' death: got in my way.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.12' title="The Mansion Family">
Doctor: Mr. Burns, I'm afraid you are the sickest man in the United States. You have everything.
Mr. Burns: You mean I have pneumonia?
Doctor: Yes.
Mr. Burns: Juvenile diabetes?
Doctor: Yes.
Mr. Burns: Hysterical pregnancy?!
Doctor: Uh, a little bit, yes. You also have thousands of diseases that have just been discovered, in you.
Mr. Burns: You're sure you haven't just made thousands of mistakes? 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.13' title="Saddlesore Galactica">
Wiggum: This is clearly a case of animal cruelty. Uh, do you have a permit for that?
Barker: No problem, sir, it's in my car. [gets in, and quickly drives off]
</quote>
<quote epno='11.13' title="Saddlesore Galactica">
Lou:You've gotta stop being so trusting, Chief.
Chief Wiggum: I'd rather let a thousand guilty men go free than chase after them.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.13' title="Saddlesore Galactica">
Chief Wiggum: All right, show's over, folks. I'm afraid this horse is going to the dog food factory.
Homer: Good luck getting a horse to eat dog food. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.14' title="Alone Again, Natura-Diddily">
Homer: Now, now, now, don't beat yourself up. I'm the one who drove her out of her seat. I'm the one who provoked the lethal barrage of T-shirts. I'm the one who parked in the ambulance zone, preventing any possible resuscitation. [notices Ned glaring at him] Yeah, I, uh, but there's no point in playing the blame game. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.14' title="Alone Again, Natura-Diddily">
Homer: I'm sure your wife is dating a lot of people in heaven!
Ned: Are you sure?
Homer: Positive, there's a lot of hot people up there. There's John Wayne, Tupac Shakur, Sherlock Holmes-
Ned: Ah, now Sherlock Holmes is a character.
Homer: Oh he sure was! [does a sexy growl] 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.15' title="Missionary: Impossible">
Bart: You're watching PBS?
Homer: Hey, I'm as surprised as you. But I've stumbled across a delicious new comedy about soccer hooligans. If they're not having a go with a bird, they're having a row with a wanker.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.15' title="Missionary: Impossible">
Homer: But I don't know what to do!
Craig: Well, we taught them some English and we ridiculed away most of their beliefs. You can take it from there.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.16' title="Pygmoelian">
Moe: [after looking at his face in the year's calendar] Am I really that ugly?
Carl: Moe, it's all relative. Just like, is Lenny that dumb? [Lenny gasps] Is Barney that drunk? [Barney gasps] Is Homer that lazy, bald, and fat? [Homer gasps]
</quote>
<quote epno='11.16' title="Pygmoelian">
Moe: I've been called "Ugly," "Pug Ugly," "Fugly," "Pug Fugly." But never "Ugly-Ugly!"
</quote>
<quote epno='11.16' title="Pygmoelian">
    Lisa: [reading from a sticker] A gay president for 2084?
    Gay Man: We're realistic. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.17' title="Bart to the Future">
    Homer Simpson: Oh, what a bleak and horrible future we live in!
    Bart Simpson: Don't you mean "present?"
    Homer Simpson: Right, right. Present. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.17' title="Bart to the Future">

    Marge Simpson: [The Simpsons have a family meal at the White House, now that Lisa is President.] So, how was everyone's day?
    Lisa Simpson: Appointed a Supreme Court justice.
    Bart Simpson: Bewitched marathon.
    Homer Simpson: Searched for Lincoln's gold.
    Lisa Simpson: Dad, that's just a myth. Lincoln didn't bury any gold in the White House.
    Homer Simpson: Then what is his ghost protecting?
</quote>
<quote epno='11.18' title="Days of Wine and D'oh'ses">
    Homer: I can't believe I found this muscle shirt.
    Bart: Dad, that's a sports bra.
    Homer: All I know is that I'm getting the support I need. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.18' title="Days of Wine and D'oh'ses">
    Bart: You did it, Dad!
    Homer: [drunk] You can't prove I did it.
    Lisa: No, you saved our lives.
    Homer: I could do a lot of things if I had some money. 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.19' title="Kill the Alligator and Run">
    Doctor: What you need is a good, long rest. I suggest Florida.
    Homer: Florida? But that's America's wang!
    Doctor: They prefer, "The Sunshine State." 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.19' title="Kill the Alligator and Run">
    Bart: Hey, this isn't real. This is printed by the Montana Militia.
    Homer [threateningly]: It'll be real soon enough! 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.19' title="Kill the Alligator and Run">
Homer: Arizona smells funny.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.20' title="Last Tap Dance in Springfield">
Ralph: My daddy shoots people!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.20' title="Last Tap Dance in Springfield">
Homer: For an evening or a week, there's no place like the mall. Food, fun and fashion, the mall has it all.
</quote>
<quote epno='11.21' title="It's A Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad Marge">
Sqeaky-Voiced Teen: And God said, "Gather two of every flavor, anoint them with sixty-two sauces, whipped cream, and nuts, and ye shall call it, 'The Ark'!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.21' title="It's A Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad Marge">
Ice Cream Store Clerk: [after Marge throws sprinkles at his eyes] I can only see a horrible rainbow!
</quote>
<quote epno='11.22' title="Behind the Laughter ">
    Lisa: To prolong the run of the series, I was secretly given anti-growth hormones.
    [Camera cuts to Homer]
    Homer: That's ridiculous! How could I even get all five necessary drops into her cereal? [pause] What? 
</quote>
<quote epno='11.22' title="Behind the Laughter ">
Homer Simpson: Why did I take such punishment? Let's just say that fame was like a drug. But what was even more like a drug was the drugs.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.01' title="Treehouse of Horror XI">
    Homer: Did you see that? I did the deed, open the gates!
    St. Peter: [reading a newspaper] What? Oh sorry, I didn't see that.
    Homer: What? I thought you guys saw everything!
    St. Peter: No, you're thinking of Santa Claus.
    Homer: Well I'll be damned!
    St. Peter: Afraid so. [pulls a cord, sending Homer to Hell] 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.01' title="Treehouse of Horror XI">
    Dolphin: Your majesty! You're free at last!
    Snorky: They made me do tricks like a common seal! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.02' title="A Tale of Two Springfields">
    Bart: C'mon, Lis, there's gotta be a way to lure that badger out.
    Lisa: Well, according to whatbadgerseat.com, badgers subsist primarily on a diet of stoats, voles, and marmots.
    Bart: [hunts through the kitchen cabinets] Hmm, stoats... stoats ...
    Lisa: Stoats are weasels, Bart. They don't come in cans.
    Bart: Then what's this? [triumphantly holds up a can]
    Lisa: That says corn, Bart.
    Bart: Must you embarrass me? 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.02' title="A Tale of Two Springfields">
    Kent Brockman: [about "New Springfield"] Scientists say they're also less attractive physically, and while we speak in a well-educated manner they tend to use low-brow expressions like "oh yeah?" and "come here a minute!"
    Homer: Oh yeah? They think they're better than us, huh?! Bart, come here a minute.
    Bart: You come here a minute!
    Homer: Oh yeah? 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.03' title="Insane Clown Poppy">
    Stephen King: I'm working on a biography of Benjamin Franklin. He's a fascinating man. He discovered electricity and used it to torture small animals and innocent babies. And that key he tied to the end of a kite? It opened the gates of HELL! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.03' title="Insane Clown Poppy">
    Marge: Look, Maggie. Christopher Walken's reading "Goodnight Moon"!
    Christopher Walken: "Goodnight room. Goodnight moon. Goodnight cow jumping over the moon!" [children listening slowly back away terrified] Please, children, scootch closer. Don't make me tell you again about the scootching. You in the red, chop chop. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.03' title="Insane Clown Poppy">
    Marge: Homer that's not prayer that's gossip.
    Homer: Fine I'll discuss heavenly matters. [to God] So how's Maude Flanders doing up there, is she playing the field? Heh heh. Really all those guys? [family stares at him in shock] Amen. [starts eating] 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.03' title="Insane Clown Poppy">
Krusty: Listen, kid, I'm not the kind of dad who, you know, does things, or says stuff or looks at ya. But the love is there!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.03' title="Insane Clown Poppy">
Homer: Hey, I said I was sorry. [As he's running from the mob shooting at him.]
The mob: Well, in that case we'll stop. What a class act and nice guy. [They stop shooting.] 
Homer: Sorry you are such jerks.[ They begin shooting at him again]
</quote>
<quote epno='12.04' title="Lisa the Tree Hugger">
    Homer: [to Jesse, referring to Lisa's predicament] This is your fault, with your non-threatening Bobby-Sherman-style good looks! No girl could resist your charms!
    Jesse: This was her choice, Mr. Simpson.
    Homer: I'm sorry, I wasn't listening. I was lost in your eyes.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.04' title="Lisa the Tree Hugger">
Jesse: I'm a level five vegan -- I won't eat anything that casts a shadow
</quote>
<quote epno='12.05' title="Homer vs. Dignity">
    Marge: When did we become the bottom rung of society?
    Homer: I think it was when that cold snap killed off all the hobos. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.05' title="Homer vs. Dignity">
Kent Brockman: Whether you're Christian, or just non-Jewish, everyone loves Santa Claus!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.06' title="The Computer Wore Menace Shoes">
    Number 2: [to his female assistant after Homer bursts a giant bubble designed to stop him leaving]: Why did you think a big balloon would stop people?
    Assistant: Shut up! That's why! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.06' title="The Computer Wore Menace Shoes">
    Wiggum: In the interest of our public safety, we have confiscated every bagel, donut, cruder, and bearclaw in the city. And some coffee.
    Phil: Yesterday, Mr. X reported that your own department-- [Cut off by Wiggum]
    Wiggum: I know. I know. But, I can assure the police do not take prisoners out of their cells and race them... Anymore.
    Phil: What about using the electric chair to cook chicken?
    Wiggum: All right, this press conference is over! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.07' title="The Great Money Caper">
Grampa: This scam was in "The Sting Part 2," so nobody knows about it.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.07' title="The Great Money Caper">
Grampa: I can finally afford a crazy stripper wife!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.07' title="The Great Money Caper">
Ralph Wiggum: [Covered in fake blood] I look like cable TV!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
    Kent Brockman: Roads closed, pipes frozen, albinos...virtually invisible. The National Weather Service has upgraded Springfield's blizzard from "Winter Wonderland" to a "Class 3 Kill-Storm"!
    Marge: I don't like the sound of that "class 3". 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
    Marge: This terrible! How will the kids get home?
    Homer: I dunno. Internet? 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
    Skinner: Yeech. It's getting ugly out there. What would Superintendent Chalmers do? [Chalmers appears in his mind]
    Chalmers: Skinner!
    Skinner: Eh, that's no good. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
Bart: 'Underachiever and proud of it." How old is this thing?
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
Nelson: [After finding Skinner] There you are! [Over walkie-talkie] Falcon to Eagle, have located Bag of Crap.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.08' title="Skinner's Sense of Snow">
    Skinner: Nelson, if you get me out of this I have a hall monitor position opening in the Spring.
    Nelson: I spit on your monitors.
    Skinner: I know. That's why the position's avalible.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.09' title="HOMЯ">
    Doctor: Mr. Simpson, this procedure could drastically increase your brain power, or it could possibly kill you.
    Homer: Hmmm... Increase my killing power, eh? Let's do it! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.09' title="HOMЯ">
    Automated Phone System: For automated stock prices, please state the company name.
    Homer: Animotion.
    Voice: Animotion: up one and one eighth.
    Homer: Yahoo!
    Voice: Yahoo: up six and a quarter.
    Homer: Huh, what is this crap?
    Voice: Fox Broadcasting: down eight.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.09' title="HOMЯ">
    Marge: Sweetheart, a missing crayon could be anywhere.
    Homer:[crashes through the window.] Who wants lottery tickets?
    Marge: Okay. It's in his brain.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.10' title="Pokey Mom">
    Jack: Uh, which way's Mecca, I need to pray.
    Marge: Mecca?
    Jack: I'm just kidding. I'm Jewish. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.12' title="Worst Episode Ever">
Comic Book Guy: I'll pass. Beer is the nectar of the nitwit.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.12' title="Worst Episode Ever">
    Carl: Hey, you knocking beer?
    Lenny: Nobody bad mouths Duff! [Breaks a Duff bottle against the counter causing the whole bottle to break off]
    Lenny: Ahhh, piece of crap.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.12' title="Worst Episode Ever">
    Homer: Come on, you're here to make friends.
    Comic Book Guy: Oh please. If I wanted to hear mindless droning I would befriend an air conditioner.
    Moe: Oh now he's ragging on air conditioners.
    Carl: Hey they keep us cool in the summer pal!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.12' title="Tennis the Menace">
    Homer: It'll be nice to entertain friends and have people over.
    Flanders: Hey ya got a tennis court?
    Homer: Keep walking Flanders.
    Flanders: Will do.
    Homer: Faster! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.12' title="Tennis the Menace">
    Kent Brockman: That's game set and match, but the real winner here are Marge's hors d'oeuvres.
    Homer: Wow, how do you come up with such witty remarks?
    Kent Brockman: [nervous laughing] Well... [Zoom's in on Brockman's ear piece, static is heard] [Shows a car outside where two writers are typing]
    Writer 1: Come on hurry up. [Writer 2 gives him a newly typed note] I guess you could say it's my racket.
    Kent Brockman: I guess you could say I'm Iraqi.
    Homer: [gasps] [threatening tone] Get off my property. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.13' title="Day of the Jackanapes">
    Marge: I think it's good for a show to retire before it gets old and stale.
    Smithers: [walks in tired] Maggie shot Mr.Burns again! [the family stares blankly at Smithers] 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.13' title="Day of the Jackanapes">
    Sideshow Bob is trying to hypnotise Bart
    Sideshow Bob: You are in my power.
    Bart: I am at your command.
    Sideshow Bob: I didn't say anything about command. If you are in my power, say so.
    Bart: I am in your power.
    Sideshow Bob: Excellent. Actually, go back to command. No... power, power! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.13' title="Day of the Jackanapes">
    Sideshow Bob: Rakes! My old archenemy
    Bart: I thought I was your archenemy?
    Sideshow Bob: I have a life outside of you, Bart. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.14' title="New Kids on the Blecch ">
    L.T. Smash: I want you to meet and greet the other members of the Party Posse. He's smart, he's soulful, he's Milhouse! [someone spins a chair around to reveal Milhouse, with a new haircut and hipper clothing]
    Milhouse: What up, G-money?
</quote>
<quote epno='12.14' title="New Kids on the Blecch ">
    L.T. Smash: Next: He'll break your nose, your glasses, and your heart - Nelson. [spins chair to reveal Nelson]
    Bart: Wait, these are just guys from school. Who's next, Ralph Wiggum?
    Ralph: [spins his own chair around] Whee! I'm a pop sensation!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.15' title="Hungry, Hungry Homer">
    Ghost of César Chávez: I am the spirit of César Chávez.
    Homer: Then why do you look like César Romero?
    Ghost of César Chávez: Because you don't know what César Chávez looks like.
</quote>
<quote epno='12.16' title="Byr Bye Nerdie">
    Homer: [after Lisa gets punched in the face by the new girl in school] Oh, Lisa, I know how you feel. Did you know that when I was in grade school, I had a bully problem myself? [whip pan past a screen full of hippie daisies and psychedelic colors to the 1970s where a preteen Homer has a preteen Smithers pinned to a wall of lockers with his fist drawn back]    
Teenage Homer: [siging] Everybody was [as he's punching Smithers in the stomach] kung-fu-fighting! [Smithers moans as a preteen Barney Gumble accompanies Homer's singing with a few notes on his recorder]
Teenage Homer: (continues singing): Those cats were (as he's punching Smithers in the stomach again): fast-as-lightning! [Smithers moans again. Homer finishes off his performance by punching the glasses off Smithers' face]
    Homer: [in the present] Good times. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.17' title="Simpson Safari">
    Homer: Okay, here's the situation: We're hopelessly lost and about to die. [a crocodile roars up from the river. The family screams]
    Homer: Don't worry! Being eaten by a crocodile is just like going to sleep... in a giant blender. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.17' title="Simpson Safari">
    Homer: 'Gopher jerky'? 'Cream of Toast'? Where do we get this crap?
    Marge: Mostly they were from relatives who couldn't see very well. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.18' title="Trilogy of Error">
    Wiggum: [answering phone] 9-1-1. This'd better be good.
    Marge: I just cut off my husband's thumb!
    Wiggum: ATTEMPTED MURDER?! YOU'LL BURN FOR THIS! BURN IN JAIL!
    Marge: It was an accident!
    Wiggum: Yeah, yeah. Save it for "Dateline: Tuesday." Uh, what's your address so I can come arrest you?
    Marge: Arrest me? Um, my address, it's um, 1-2-3 ... Fake Street.
    Wiggum: [writing address down] 1-2-3 Fake Street. Okay see you soon! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.18' title="Trilogy of Error">
Dr. Nick Riviera: Inflammable means flammable? What a country!
</quote>
<quote epno='12.19' title="I'm Goin' to Praiseland">
    Rich Texan: May the Lord have mercy on your gas-sniffin' orphan-beatin' souls.
    Homer: Christ be with you. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.20' title="Children of a Lesser Clod">
    Homer: [in a video of him chasing Bart down the street with a chain mace] I'LL MACE YOU GOOD!
    Bart: AAAAAHHH!!
    Homer: Hey! That is completely taken out of context. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.20' title="Children of a Lesser Clod">
    Flanders: So, did you boys have a good time?
    Rod: Yeah, Mr. Simpson was really funny.
    Todd: He told us how the world keeps screwing him over. 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.20' title="Children of a Lesser Clod">
    Arnie Pie: (describing Homer's actions) He's jumping out of the car, Kent! He's trying to climb over the fence! Now he's realizing he's too fat. He's digging a hole like a dog. Now he's given up on that and he' running back and forth. He's climbing into a pipe and he seems to be stuck. His legs are dangling in a comical fashion. Oh, it's the saddest thing I've ever seen.
    Kent Brockman: Arnie, Arnie, how are the children?
    Arnie Pie: I can't see through metal, Kent! 
</quote>
<quote epno='12.21' title="Simpsons Tall Tales">
    Hobo: Don't worry, I'm not a stabbing hobo, I'm a singing hobo.
</quote>
<quote epno='13.01' title="Treehouse of Horror XII">
Homer: Ah, Ethnictown. Where hard-working immigrants dream of becoming lazy, overfed Americans.
</quote>
<quote epno='13.01' title="Treehouse of Horror XII">
    Bart: Awww, we're all out of milk!
    Lisa: [takes wand out] Abra-Ka-Dairy. [milk appears out of thin air and pours into Bart's cereal]
    Marge: [rushes in] Come on kids, we're gonna be late for wizards' school!
    Lisa: [points wand at clock] Five-Minutes-Morious. [clock goes back five minutes]
    Marge: [worried, looking at the clock] That can't be good for the clock. 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.02' title="The Parent Rap">
    Harm: Silence in my courtroom! [reads docket] Grand theft auto?
    Bart: It was an accident, ma'am.
    Harm: Don't spit on my cupcake and tell me it's frosting! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.02' title="The Parent Rap">
    Harm: Silence in my courtroom! [reads docket] Grand theft auto?
Marge: I don't mean to be disrespectful Judge Harm, but we are not bad parents. And there isn't a tether in this world with enough fiber optics to make me say that we are.
</quote>
<quote epno='13.03' title="Homer the Moe">
    Moe: Ah, who am I kidding. I ain't smiled for real since I nailed that rat with the icepick. Heh. Remember that?
    Homer: That was an amazing throw. 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.03' title="Homer the Moe">
    Homer: I'll throw myself out, thank you.
    [He grabs his shirt collar, yanks himself toward the front door, and tosses himself to the street]
    Homer: I believe I had a hat!
    [Someone throws him a hat]
    Homer: SUCKERS!!! [runs away laughing]
</quote>
<quote epno='13.03' title="Homer the Moe">
       Homer: [R.E.M. are playing in Homer's garage. Homer is singing along to 'It's the End of the World as We Know It (And I Feel Fine)'] Leonardo What's-His-Name, Herman Munster, motorcade, birthday parties, Cheetos, pogo sticks and lemonade! You symbiotic, stupid jerk! That's right, Flanders, I am talking about you! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.04' title="A Hunka Hunka Burns in Love">
    Mr. Burns: I don't understand. She was my young sexy fiance and he was my sexually virile best friend and they just drove off in my Bugatti Sexarossa.
    Kent Brockman: Well, according to our audience insta-poll, 46% say "You're too old", and 37% say "She's a skank!". 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.04' title="A Hunka Hunka Burns in Love">
    Homer: [at Snake's hideout] Wow, who do you have to kill to get a place like this?
    Snake: I think his name was "Gustafsson."
</quote>
<quote epno='13.05' title="The Blunder Years">
    Lenny: Is that Wacky Tobacky?
    Fat Tony: The wackiest. 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.05' title="The Blunder Years">
    Marge: You found a corpse when you were twelve? No wonder you've been so traumatized.
    Homer: It's responsible for everything wrong in my life...my occasional overeating...my fear of corpses! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.06' title="She of Little Faith">
    Nelson: Hey Simpson, I hear your sister dumped Christianity!
    Bart: Who cares?
    Dolph: I'll tell you someone who cares. He's got long hair, works as a carpenter, has a lot of crazy ideas about love and brotherhood!
</quote>
<quote epno='13.06' title="She of Little Faith">
    Lisa: I'm not gonna pick a religion just because it sounds cool.
    Bart: How about Judaism? When you turn thirteen, cha-ching! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.07' title="Brawl in the Family">
Willie: [acid rain is falling; singing] I'm singin' in the rain! Just singin' in the rain! What a glorious feeling -- argh! [collapses on the ground, as his overalls dissolve] It burns like a Glasgow bikini wax!
</quote>
<quote epno='13.07' title="Brawl in the Family">
Homer: [drunk] Look, the think about my family is, there's five of us: Marge, Bart, girl-Bart, the one who doesn't talk, and the fat guy. How I loathe him. [falls off the barstool]
</quote>
<quote epno='13.08' title="Sweets and Sour Marge">
Homer: (After being told Springfield is now officially "the world's fattest city" and looking directly into the camera) In your face, Milwaukee!!
</quote>
<quote epno='13.09' title="Jaws Wired Shut">
    Homer: Looks like I need some fuel for me mule, gas for me ass! (Popeye-like laughter) 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.11' title="The Bart Wants What It Wants">
    Lisa: [As Homer is about to cross the road]" Dad, no! The sign says 'Don't walk'!
    Homer: That's okay, they have free health care. "[Gets sent flying by an oncoming car]" I'm rich! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.12' title="The Lastest Gun in the West">
    Nelson: [Bart enters the classroom in torn clothes]Ha ha, Bart's family is poor! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.14' title="Tales from the Public Domain">
    Suitor (Krusty): We came here when Helen of Troy was hot!
    Helen of Troy (Agnes)a la Phyllis Diller: This is the face that launched a thousand ships... the other way! 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.14' title="Tales from the Public Domain">
    Lisa: [gasps] What happened Dad? They didn't really burn her did they?
    Marge: [hastily grabs the Book from Homer] Of course not, Honey. "Just then, Sir Lancelot rode up on a white horse and saved Joan of Arc. They got married and lived in a space ship. The End."[ Tears out the page and begins eating it] Well, it's easier to chew than that Bambi video. 
</quote>
<quote epno='13.15' title="Blame it on Lisa">
Dance Instructor: Here is where we invented the Lambada and the Macarena. Now we are working on our new dance: La Penetrada! It makes Sex look like a church!
</quote>
</quotelist>
